This XML file does not appear to have any style information associated with it. The document tree is shown below.
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Web3 Jobs API https://web3.career</title>
<link>https://web3.career/web3-jobs-api</link>
<description>API Terms of Service: Please link back using apply_url (with follow, and without nofollow!) and mention web3.career as a source, so we get traffic back from your site. If you do not we'll have to suspend API access.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<ttl>60</ttl>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49724</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 5 May 2023 04:41:18 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Information Security Manager, Compliance</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QjM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="single-job-content body3 block" id="tabpanel-0" aria-labelledby="tab-0" role="tabpanel"> <div class="content-intro"> <p><span>At Ripple, we’re building a world where value moves like information does today. It’s big, it’s bold, and we’re already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs. </span></p> <p><span>If you’re ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.</span></p> </div> <div> <p><strong>THE WORK:</strong></p> <p><span>Through our blockchain technology and rapidly growing network of financial institutions, Ripple is improving the global financial system and increasing economic inclusion for more people, in more places around the world.  Ripple is looking for passionate Information Security professionals to build a world class Information Security program.  As part of the Information Security team, you will help us achieve this mission by actively working to protect our staff, company, and the larger crypto communities we engage with.  </span></p> <p><strong>WHAT YOU’LL DO:</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>Examine, evaluate, and document internal controls based on various security standards (NIST CSF, MAS, ITGC, SOC2, ISO-27001, etc.)</span></li> <li><span>Lead IT-related audits and examinations conducted by external parties</span></li> <li><span>Align policies, standards and procedures with compliance objectives</span></li> <li><span>Prepare metrics and reports for management on the status of GRC objectives</span></li> <li><span>Evaluate and respond to customer/prospect questions and audits. Assist in aligning compliance reports and public-facing Trust Page to reduce the overall number of customer requests</span></li> <li><span>Remain up to date on current security laws, regulations and standards</span></li> <li><span>Represent the GRC Team by participating directly with projects and provide guidance, requirements and documentation for security-related purposes when requested</span></li> <li><span>Create, evaluate, document and maintain standards, processes and procedures relative to security and privacy</span></li> <li><span>Engage with management to identify possible resolutions to control weaknesses and opportunities for improvement.</span></li> <li><span>Perform GRC recurring tasks as required </span></li> <li><span>Provide consultative guidance and oversight to project teams to design, develop, deploy and sustain solutions that meet compliance requirements, including but not limited to a set of technical deliverables, cost, schedule, quality, and status reporting</span></li> <li><span>Assist in selecting, configuring and/or administering program via GRC tools</span></li> <li><span>Assist with building and/or testing integrations and automations with SaaS/IaaS platforms to collect evidence for security audits and monitor for security configurations</span></li> <li><span>Assist with developing configuration monitoring capabilities for SaaS and IaaS platforms</span></li> </ul> <p> </p> </div> <div> <p><strong>WHAT YOU'LL BRING: </strong></p> </div> <div> <ul> <li><span>Degree or equivalent in Computer Science or related field</span></li> <li><span>7 years of experience in Information Security with a specialization in one area of GRC </span></li> <li><span>A broad understanding of security domains</span></li> <li><span>Experience working with engineering teams to understand issues and prioritize remediations</span></li> <li><span>Experience with Money Transmitter License (MTL) regulatory standards and audits and ITGC Control audits</span></li> <li><span>Proficiency with common information security frameworks including SOC2, NIST CSF, and ISO 27001</span></li> <li><span>Demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively across teams </span></li> <li><span>Demonstrated organizational, project management and documentation skills </span></li> <li><span>Familiarity and experience with IT/Security/GRC toolset, such as : Jira, Confluence, integrated GRC platforms etc.</span></li> <li><span>Ability to analyze empirical evidence and technical reports, identify root causes, work with teams to identify solutions to remediate gaps. </span></li> <li><span>Familiarly with different cloud concepts and tooling including AWS, GCP </span></li> <li><span>Experience in a remote-first and distributed environment</span></li> <li><span>Someone willing to adapt to change in a fast moving environment</span></li> <li><span>Experience with cloud-native pre-IPO startup companies</span></li> <li><span>Experience with AWS security services and tooling</span></li> <li><span>Desirable certifications:  CISSP, CISA, PMP</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Other common names for this role: </span></p> </div> <div class="content-conclusion"> <hr> <p><strong>WHO WE ARE:</strong></p> <p><span>Do Your Best Work</span></p> <ul> <li><span>The opportunity to build in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders</span></li> <li><span>A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact.  A professional development budget to support other modes of learning.</span></li> <li><span>Thrive in an environment where no matter what race, ethnicity, gender, origin, or culture they identify with, every employee is a respected, valued, and empowered part of the team.</span></li> <li><span>Ripple is Flexible First: you have the option to work from home, from our offices, or a combination of the two around our centers of gravity (15 global offices).</span></li> <li><span>Weekly all-company meeting - business updates and ask me anything &gt;</span></li> <li><span>We come together for moments that matter which include team offsites, team bonding activities, happy hours and more!</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Control of Your Finances</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Competitive salary, bonuses, and equity</span></li> <li><span>Competitive benefits that cover physical and mental healthcare, retirement, family forming, and family support</span></li> <li><span>Employee giving match</span></li> <li><span>Mobile phone stipend</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Care of Yourself</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Twice a quarter R&amp;R days so you can rest and recharge</span></li> <li><span>Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite &amp; virtual programming</span></li> <li><span>Generous vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it</span></li> <li><span>Industry-leading parental leave policies. Family planning benefits.</span></li> <li><span>Catered lunches, fully-stocked kitchens with premium snacks/beverages, and plenty of fun events</span></li> </ul> <p><span><em data-stringify-type="italic">Benefits listed above are for full-time employees.</em></span></p> <hr> <div><em>Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.</em></div> <div> </div> <div><em>Please find our UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice and our California Applicant Privacy Notice for reference.</em></div> </div> <p></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Ripple</company>
<location>Toronto, Canada</location>
<tags>compliance, non-tech, security, aws, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49716</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 23:07:30 +0700</pubDate>
<title>DeFi Trader</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=YTM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Remote<br><br>Full-time<br><br>We are seeking a talented DeFi Trader to join our team at Immuna. Our startup provides institutional investors with a platform to manage their risks of investing in digital assets. We help protect investors' digital asset investments from unexpected exploits and economic risks by monitoring the market and proactively defending their investments.<br><br>As a DeFi Trader at Immuna, you will develop and implement highly effective strategies that extract value from digital asset chains and their underlying protocols. You will stay up to date with new developments in the DeFi space to create new strategies and enhance existing ones<br><br>Qualifications:<br></p><ul> <li>Bachelor's degree in finance, economics, computer science, or a related field. </li> <li>Proven experience in DeFi trading, with a strong understanding of node infrastructure (Tendermint, Geth, etc.). </li> <li>Knowledge of major DeFi protocols and their inner workings. </li> <li>Knowledge of the mempool and transaction ordering. </li> <li>Familiarity with digital assets and blockchain technology. </li> <li>Strong analytical and quantitative skills. </li> <li>Excellent communication and interpersonal skills. </li> <li>Ability to work independently and as part of a team. <br><br> </li> </ul>Responsibilities:<br><ul> <li>Identify and propose compelling investment opportunities for review and decision making. </li> <li>Optimize the execution of trade ideas with a clear, detail-oriented approach. </li> <li>Conduct research on potential investments, including reviewing app documentation and smart contract audits, and ask critical questions to founders. </li> <li>Maintain and optimize Defi strategies, including regular checks on approvals and the transfer of idle funds from exchanges. </li> <li>Develop and implement highly effective strategies to extract value from digital asset chains and their underlying protocols. </li> <li>Stay up to date with new developments in the DeFi space to create new strategies and enhance existing ones. </li> <li>Utilize your creativity and research skills to discover new opportunities for MEV. <br><br> </li> </ul>Compensation Range: $120K - $200K<br><br> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Immuna</company>
<location> CA San Francisco US</location>
<tags>trader, blockchain, defi, node</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49711</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 21:40:30 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Mid-Market Customer Success Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ETM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<section id="job-openings" class="job-openings"> <div class="container"> <div class="content-intro"><p><em>Founded in 2018 and already valued at over $8 billion, Fireblocks is a SaaS platform that helps companies to create innovative products on the blockchain and manage day-to-day crypto operations. Fireblocks is trusted by some of the largest financial institutions, banks, globally-recognized brands, and Web3 companies in the world, including BNY Mellon, BNP Paribas, ANZ Bank, Revolut, and thousands more, to securely scale digital asset operations through the Fireblocks Network and MPC-based wallet infrastructure. We have offices in New York, London, Tel Aviv, and Singapore, and we are continuing to expand our teams to reach new customers globally.</em></p></div> <h4><span>What you'll do</span></h4> <p><span>As a Mid-Market Customer Success Manager at Fireblocks you'll work with our customers on engagement programs that will impact large target customer groups. You'll build processes and manage the life-cycle of Fireblocks strategic customers, build great relationships, demonstrate the product, educate customers, represent the customer interest by managing feature requests with product management, and prioritize support cases. You'll have the opportunity to learn the ins and outs of the cyber and digital asset world and master our groundbreaking product while becoming a source of knowledge and an expert on our system.</span></p> <h4><span>Responsibilities</span></h4> <ul> <li><span>Own the post-sale processes, accompanying Fireblocks’ customers’ implementation, and post-onboarding processes.</span></li> <li><span>Collaborate closely with team members to support renewals and expansion opportunities.</span></li> <li><span>Leverage tools and technology to deliver value to multiple accounts at once through 1:many programs, such as leading customer campaigns, custom training/webinars, and hosting online workshops to educate customers on the features of Fireblocks products.</span></li> <li><span>Help build and shape the Mid-Market Customer Success team at Fireblocks, and drive innovation and best practices.</span></li> </ul> <h4><span>Minimum Requirements</span></h4> <ul> <li><span>3+ years of experience as a customer success manager (or similar role) </span></li> <li><span>Experience in scaling in a hyper-growth company, and a deep understanding of the SaaS business model </span></li> <li><span>Excellent communication, influence, and presentation skills </span></li> <li><span>Strong sense of urgency, with a willingness to be available at non-routine hours </span></li> <li><span>A true autodidact with amazing interpersonal skills and technical acumen</span></li> <li><span>Knowledge in the Crypto\Blockchain field is highly desired</span></li> </ul> <p><span>For employees hired to work remotely from New York, or from our NYC HQ, Fireblocks is required by law to include a reasonable estimate of the compensation range for this role.</span></p> <p><span>This range is specific to New York City and takes into consideration a wide range of factors that are reviewed when making a hiring decision, such as years of experience, skills, and other business needs.</span></p> <p><span>It is not typical for a candidate to be hired at or near the top of the pay range and each compensation decision is dependent on each individual case. A reasonable base salary range estimate for this position is $97,000 </span><span>to $</span><span>154,000</span><span>. The base salary is one component of the total compensation package, which for some roles may include a target bonus, a very competitive equity grant, and very generous benefits. While we believe competitive compensation is a critical aspect of you deciding to join us, we do hope you also spend time considering why our mission and culture are right for you. We are creating something transformational here, and we hope you are as excited about the future as we are.</span></p> <div class="content-conclusion"> <p><em>Fireblocks' mission is to enable every business to easily and securely access digital assets and cryptocurrencies. In order to do that, we strongly believe our workforce should be as diverse as our clients, and this is why we embrace diversity and inclusion in all its forms. </em></p> <h6><em>Please see our candidate privacy policy here.</em></h6> </div> <div id="grnhse_app"></div> </div> </section> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Fireblocks</company>
<location>Location: New York</location>
<tags>customer-success, sales, non-tech, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49706</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 20:18:35 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Communications Director </title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=YDM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p><strong>Communications Director </strong></p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>About This Position </strong></p> <p><br></p> <p>High Vibe PR  is a boutique communications firm for companies and brands that redefine the future of culture and entertainment. We’ve announced the world’s largest gaming fund, placed creators in genre-crossing media, launched numerous Web3 games, and handled the crisis comms for the world’s biggest crypto hack. We are rapidly expanding and are in search of kind comms professionals who believe in ownership, teamwork, and the power of blockchain technology. </p> <p><br></p> <p>We are seeking a <strong>Communications Director</strong>. This is a remote, full-time position. We are digital nomads looking for someone based in CEST and EST time zones only.</p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>Responsibilities: </strong></p> <ul> <li>Provide strategic and tactical PR contributions including drafting press releases, writing pitches, as well as managing media relationships;</li> <li>Work with clients on announcements, evergreen stories, and proactive stories to meet client goals;</li> <li>Collaborate with Founder to support PR activations from concept to execution including planning, project management, execution, and reporting;</li> <li>Identify executive positioning opportunities for clients including speaking engagements and thought leadership moments; </li> <li>Manage administrative tasks such as internal project management, client call notes, monthly recaps, and reporting;</li> <li>Lead weekly client calls and staff interviews, as needed</li> </ul> <p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p> <ul> <li>BA in Communications, Journalism, Marketing, or a related field</li> <li>5-8+ years experience in a comparable PR agency experience</li> <li>Significant record in placing stories in major media outlets </li> <li>Interest in crypto, Web3, NFTs, and gaming</li> <li>Established relationships with press and key industry professionals</li> <li>Strong verbal, written, and interpersonal communication skills</li> <li>Strong organizational and project management skills </li> <li>Native English speaker<br><br> </li> </ul> <p><strong>About High Vibe PR </strong></p> <p>High Vibe PR is a boutique communications firm for companies and brands at the intersection of gaming and entertainment. As a small (but mighty!) team we act as an extension of our clients’ teams and as a trusted advisor. We work with a small number of clients so that we can go deeper with each client and do work that provides incredible value. Our work goes beyond traditional PR to shape stories that create impact and define brands as industry standouts.<br><br></p> <p><strong>What We Offer</strong></p> <ul> <li>In charge of your own destiny. We are a small team - we don’t play politics, aren’t buried in bureaucracy, and have agency over our schedules and location.</li> <li>No assholes. Life is too short to deal with oversized egos. When evaluating clients, we first look at whether the client is someone we want to work with on a daily basis.</li> <li>Supported. Our goal is to empower not only our clients, but also our team members. We recognize and encourage the importance of life outside of the office, and we've fostered a culture where we support one another.</li> </ul> <p><br>If you want to apply, please send a copy of your CV, links to your three most recent media placements, and a cover letter to Tiffany@highvibepr.com with  ‘<strong>Communications Director Role’ </strong>as the subject line.<br><br></p> <p><strong>Salary </strong></p> <p>80-120k USD, depending on experience.</p> <p><br></p> <p><br><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>High Vibe PR</company>
<location>Remote - EST or CEST timezone only</location>
<tags>pr, non-tech, executive, marketing-communication, remote, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49704</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 19:19:59 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Business Development Manager BDM</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QDM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <div>We are looking for an experienced <strong>Business Development Manager</strong> at NFT Studios, to help the company and its many projects in the web3 space to grow via the acquisition of new customers and the closing of new partnerships.  <br><br> </div> <div> <strong>Responsibilities and tasks:<br></strong><br> </div> <ul> <li>Processing current leads so they transform in new customers for our project based businesses and our soon to be released SaaS business.</li> <li>Creation of a Business Development team in the short run.</li> <li>Implementation of a CRM.</li> <li>Creation of efficient and precise sales processes.</li> <li>Input from customers to adjust current offerings accordingly.</li> </ul> <div> <strong>Requirements<br></strong><br> </div> <ul> <li>+7 years of experience in Sales departments of B2B digital products.</li> <li>Master’s degree or equivalent experience.</li> <li>Experience in managing sales teams.</li> <li>Experience working in large companies or fast growing start-ups</li> <li>Experience in the definition and interpretation of relevant marketing KPIs.</li> <li>Availability to travel regularly.</li> <li>Proactivity and “startup” mentality.</li> <li>Ambitious, yet good team player.</li> <li>Basic knowledge of the cryptocurrencies market.</li> <li>Experience and knowledge of NFTs and the Metaverse is appreciated.</li> <li>Fluent in English.</li> <li>Fluency in Spanish is a plus.</li> <li>Full commitment to the project and willingness to go the extra mile.</li> </ul> <div> <strong>What we offer:<br></strong><br> </div> <ul> <li>100% remote position (based in Barcelona or Madeira, Portugal)</li> <li>Training Opportunities.</li> <li>Work in a pleasant and friendly environment.</li> <li>Opportunities to grow professionally in the company.</li> <li>Make an impact with your work from anywhere in the world.</li> <li>Learn about Blockchain technology, Crypto Assets and the Metaverse.</li> </ul> <div> <strong>Type of contract:<br></strong><br> </div> <div>We offer a Full time position.<br><br> </div> <div>Apply by sending your CV to jobs@nftstudios.io<br><br> </div> <div><br></div> <div>—--------------------------------------------------------------<br><br> </div> <div> <strong>About the company: <br></strong><br> </div> <div>NTF Studios is a group of companies that share a mission: <strong>To Build the Metaverse, one block at a time.</strong> We are a team of over 60 people working remotely from all over the world, developing innovative digital products, tools, and technologies to enable the NFT and Metaverse spaces to grow and thrive. <br><br> </div> <div>By leveraging Blockchain technology, we empower companies, communities, and users to start their own web3 businesses, build a strong presence in the Metaverse, create their own products, explore their creativity, and engage in new and fascinating digital experiences.<br><br> </div> <div>Take a look at our web: https://www.nftstudios.io/<br><br> </div> <div> <br><br> </div> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>NFT Studios</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>business-development, sales, non-tech, blockchain, crm, crypto, nft, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49703</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 19:09:16 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Chief Marketing Officer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MDM3kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>We are looking for an experienced <strong>Chief Marketing Officer</strong> at NFT Studios, to help the company and its many projects in the web3 space, to scale via the definition and implementation of a novel Marketing Strategy, adapted to the unique characteristics of the industry.<br><br></p> <p><strong>Responsibilities and tasks:<br></strong><br></p> <ul> <li>Creation and execution of a Marketing Strategy for a series of B2B SaaS products for Web3.</li> <li>Creation and execution of a Marketing Strategy for a tailor-made Web3 technology development studio, with a top reputation in the space.</li> <li>Definition of the corporate branding of a group of 5 companies that operate in the Web3 space.</li> <li>Determination and overseeing of the Marketing strategy of 3 subsidiaries.</li> <li>Lead generation for our SaaS products and our subsidiaries.</li> <li>Definition of a content creation and customer education strategy.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Requirements<br></strong><br></p> <ul> <li>+7 years of experience in Digital Marketing, with some of them in positions of high responsibility.</li> <li>Experience in content creation and SEO strategies.</li> <li>Experience in digital business, preferably in SaaS Businesses</li> <li>Experience working in large companies or fast growing start-ups</li> <li>Experience in the definition and interpretation of relevant marketing KPIs.</li> <li>Availability to travel at least once per quarter.</li> <li>Proactivity and “startup” mentality.</li> <li>Ambitious, yet good team player.</li> <li>Basic knowledge of the cryptocurrencies market.</li> <li>Experience and knowledge of NFTs and the Metaverse is appreciated.</li> <li>Fluent in English.</li> <li>Fluency in Spanish is a plus.</li> <li>Full commitment to the project and willingness to go the extra mile.</li> </ul> <p><strong>What we offer:<br></strong><br></p> <ul> <li>100% remote position.</li> <li>Training Opportunities.</li> <li>Work in a pleasant and friendly environment.</li> <li>Opportunities to grow both professionally and personally.</li> <li>Make an impact with your work from anywhere in the world.</li> <li>Learn about Blockchain technology, Crypto Assets and the Metaverse.</li> <li>Stock options.</li> </ul> <p><br><strong>Type of contract:<br></strong><br></p> <p>We offer a Full time position.<br><br></p> <p><br></p> <p>Apply by sending your CV to jobs@nftstudios.io<br><br>__________________________________________________________________________________________<br><strong>About the company: </strong></p> <p>NTF Studios is a group of companies that share a mission: <strong>To Build the Metaverse, one block at a time.</strong> We are a team of over 60 people working remotely from all over the world, developing innovative digital products, tools, and technologies to enable the NFT and Metaverse spaces to grow and thrive. </p> <p>By leveraging Blockchain technology, we empower companies, communities, and users to start their own web3 businesses, build a strong presence in the Metaverse, create their own products, explore their creativity, and engage in new and fascinating digital experiences.</p> <p>Take a look at our web: https://www.nftstudios.io/</p> <p><br><br></p> <p><br><br></p> <p><br><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>NFT Studios</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>cmo, executive, marketing, non-tech, blockchain, crypto, nft, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49694</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:10:19 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Social Media &amp; Events Intern</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QTO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinFlip is a leading fintech company powered by cryptocurrency. Believing everyone deserves to participate in the new digital economy, the company operates one of the world’s largest networks of cryptocurrency ATMs — with over 4,000 active kiosks — as well as an over-the-counter trading desk. In 2022, CoinFlip became an international company by expanding into Canada , and launched CoinFlip Ventures , a new initiative designed to support start-up companies.<br>CoinFlip placed No. 60 on the 2021 Inc. 5000 list of the nation’s fastest-growing private companies. CoinFlip was also named the 2021 and 2022 #1 fastest-growing company in Chicago by Crain’s Business.<br>As our growth trajectory continues, we’re looking to quickly expand all of our teams. It’s an exciting time to join CoinFlip as we’re pursuing additional business lines and continued international expansion to further cement us as a leading financial technology company.<br>Throughout the course of this internship, you will assist in the ideation and creation of social content and help with event planning and execution.<br><strong><u>Responsibilities</u></strong><br></p><ul> <li>Participate in social content brainstorms</li> <li>Assist with video creation and social post writing</li> <li>Assist with responding to comments and DMs</li> <li>Coordinate logistics for marketing events, trade shows and small meetups</li> <li>Assist in researching and securing tradeshows</li> <li>Collaborate with vendors, exhibitors, and sales team</li> <li>Other duties as assigned</li> </ul><br><strong><u>Requirements</u></strong><br><ul> <li>No prior marketing experience is required </li> <li>Strong computer skills (Word, Excel and PowerPoint required) </li> <li>Ability to organize and prioritize in a deadline-oriented environment </li> <li>Excellent interpersonal communication skills </li> <li>Sound analytical and critical thinking skills </li> <li>Strong attention to detail </li> </ul><br><strong><u>Nice To Have</u></strong><br><ul> <li>Basic knowledge of cryptocurrency and blockchains </li> <li>General passion and knowledge of fintech and crypto </li> </ul><br>Working at CoinFlip means collaborating with experienced and innovative leaders who share a clear vision and a track record of success. We offer a collaborative and positive working environment where we encourage employees to balance productivity with time to recharge. Compensation is above and beyond a typical “startup” — we offer competitive salaries, performance-based incentives, and competitive benefits for full-time employees.<br>CoinFlip values diversity in the workplace and is an equal opportunity employer committed to providing an inclusive and accessible work environment. We thank all candidates who apply, but only those selected for an interview will be contacted.<br>By applying to this role, you give express consent to CoinFlip to send you informational text (SMS) messages regarding this role and the application process. You can cancel the SMS service at any time by replying "STOP" to the text message you received. If at any time you forget what keywords are supported, just reply "HELP." Message and data rates apply. If you require a special accommodation, please let us know and we’ll work with you to meet your needs. When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Olliv By CoinFlip</company>
<location> IL Chicago US</location>
<tags>intern, entry-level, social-media, non-tech, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49693</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:10:05 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Emerging Risk Analyst</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MTO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Company Description<br><br></strong>It all started with an idea at Block in 2013. Initially built to take the pain out of peer-to-peer payments, Cash App has gone from a simple product with a single purpose to a dynamic ecosystem, developing unique financial products, including Afterpay, to provide a better way to send, spend, invest, borrow and save to our 47 million monthly active customers. We want to redefine the world’s relationship with money to make it more relatable, instantly available, and universally accessible. This is our mission, and it’s why working at Cash App means so much more than a job.<br><br>Today, Cash App has thousands of employees working globally across office and remote locations, with a culture geared toward innovation, collaboration and impact. We’ve been a distributed team since day one, and many of our roles can be done remotely from the countries where Cash App operates. No matter the location, we tailor our experience to ensure our employees are creative, productive, and happy.<br><br>Check out our locations, benefits, and more at cash.app/careers!<br><br><strong>Job Description<br><br></strong>We are looking for a Financial Crimes Emerging Risk Analyst with an understanding of BSA/AML regulations and suspicious activity reporting, experience analyzing complex data sets, and the ability to identify high-risk red flags across a variety of product types within the Cash App ecosystem.<br><br>You will sift through large amounts of data to identify patterns of high-risk activity, assess and present findings, and make recommendations that can be used by Compliance and management to improve internal processes and product controls.<br><br>You Will:<br></p><ul> <li>Apply your knowledge of AML and fraud typologies to search for red flags and patterns of high-risk activity in complex data sets</li> <li>Create queries that can be used to identify high-risk activity</li> <li>Monitor industry trends, evolving financial crimes related typologies, negative news and regulatory enforcement orders/regulatory changes that could improve Cash App</li> <li>Summarize complex matters for peers, partners, and management, and share data interpretations through written reports and presentations</li> <li>Conduct account reviews</li> <li>Open or escalate suspicious activity cases</li> <li>Partner with Risk and Data Science teams</li> <li>Maintain an understanding of Cash App products and compliance requirements<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Qualifications<br><br></strong>You Have:<br><ul> <li>2+ years experience with SQL, Python, Looker, Tableau, Excel (can perform complex functions, including query writing) or other data analysis tools</li> <li>Experience reviewing financial data or customer accounts as part of AML or fraud investigations</li> <li>Experience summarizing findings and present to peers, managers and senior members of management<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Additional Information<br><br></strong>Block takes a market-based approach to pay, and pay may vary depending on your location. U.S. locations are categorized into one of four zones based on a cost of labor index for that geographic area. The successful candidate’s starting pay will be determined based on job-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location, and market conditions. These ranges may be modified in the future.<br><br>Zone A: USD $114,200 - USD $139,600<br><br>Zone B: USD $106,200 - USD $129,800<br><br>Zone C: USD $97,100 - USD $118,700<br><br>Zone D: USD $85,700 - USD $104,700<br><br>To find a location’s zone designation, please refer to this resource. If a location of interest is not listed, please speak with a recruiter for additional information.<br><br>Benefits include the following:<br><ul> <li>Healthcare coverage</li> <li>Retirement Plans including company match </li> <li>Employee Stock Purchase Program</li> <li>Wellness programs, including access to mental health, 1:1 financial planners, and a monthly wellness allowance </li> <li>Paid parental and caregiving leave</li> <li>Paid time off</li> <li>Learning and Development resources</li> <li>Paid Life insurance, AD&amp;D. and disability benefits </li> <li>Perks such as WFH reimbursements and free access to caregiving, legal, and discounted resources <br><br> </li> </ul>This role is also eligible to participate in Block's equity plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies, and may be eligible for a sign-on bonus. Sales roles may be eligible to participate in a commission plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies. Pay and benefits are subject to change at any time, consistent with the terms of any applicable compensation or benefit plans.<br><br>We’re working to build a more inclusive economy where our customers have equal access to opportunity, and we strive to live by these same values in building our workplace. Block is a proud equal opportunity employer. We work hard to evaluate all employees and job applicants consistently, without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, pregnancy, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other legally protected class.<br><br>We believe in being fair, and are committed to an inclusive interview experience, including providing reasonable accommodations to disabled applicants throughout the recruitment process. We encourage applicants to share any needed accommodations with their recruiter, who will treat these requests as confidentially as possible. <strong><em>Want to learn more about what we’re doing to build a workplace that is fair and square? Check out our</em></strong><strong><em><u> I+D page</u></em></strong><strong><em>.<br><br></em></strong>Additionally, we consider qualified applicants with criminal histories for employment on our team, assessing candidates in a manner consistent with the requirements of the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance.<br><br><em>Block, Inc. (NYSE: SQ) is a global technology company with a focus on financial services. Made up of Square, Cash App, Spiral, TIDAL, and TBD, we build tools to help more people access the economy. Square helps sellers run and grow their businesses with its integrated ecosystem of commerce solutions, business software, and banking services. With Cash App, anyone can easily send, spend, or invest their money in stocks or Bitcoin. Spiral (formerly Square Crypto) builds and funds free, open-source Bitcoin projects. Artists use TIDAL to help them succeed as entrepreneurs and connect more deeply with fans. TBD is building an open developer platform to make it easier to access Bitcoin and other blockchain technologies without having to go through an institution.</em> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Cash App</company>
<location> CA San Francisco US</location>
<tags>analyst, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49692</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:08:43 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Business Development Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ITO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p></p><p><strong>About UNOPND</strong></p><p>UNOPND is a Web3 startup studio incubating decentralized NFT projects in the gaming and K-pop entertainment industries. Backed by the Hashed, the largest crypto fund in Korea, we are focused on nurturing innovative projects and driving the adoption of web3 technologies worldwide.</p><br><p><strong>Job Description</strong></p><p>We are seeking a highly motivated and experienced Business Development Manager to join the Global BD team. The BizDev Manager will work closely with the CBDO, supporting the growth of our incubated projects by building strategic relationships, identifying new partnership opportunities, and managing existing relationships with investors and industry stakeholders.</p><p></p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p><ul> <li><span>Develop and maintain relationships with investors, industry stakeholders, and strategic partners, ensuring successful project execution and growth.</span></li> <li>Identify and pursue new business opportunities, partnerships, and collaborations for UNOPND's incubated projects in the gaming and K-pop entertainment industries.</li> <li><span>Represent UNOPND at industry events, conferences, and networking sessions, building brand awareness and establishing relationships with potential partners and investors.</span></li> <li>Collaborate with the CBDO and project teams to define partnership strategies and set targets for fundraising, user acquisition, and market expansion.</li> <li><span>Collaborate with cross-functional teams, including product, marketing, and engineering, to align partnership objectives and support project success.</span></li> <li><span>Conduct market research and analysis to identify trends, opportunities, and potential challenges within the web3, NFT, gaming, and K-pop entertainment sectors.</span></li> </ul><br><p><strong>Qualifications</strong></p><ul> <li>Bachelor's degree or equivalent experience.</li> <li>5+ years of experience in business development, strategic partnerships, or a related role, preferably within the blockchain, <span>gaming, </span>or entertainment industries.</li> <li>Proven track record of building and maintaining strong relationships with investors, partners, and industry stakeholders.</li> <li>Excellent communication, negotiation, and interpersonal skills.</li> <li>Strong analytical and problem-solving abilities, with a data-driven approach to decision-making.</li> <li>Good understanding of web3, NFT, gaming, and K-pop entertainment trends and technologies.</li> <li>Ability to travel as needed for meetings, events, and conferences.</li> <li><span>Proficient in both English and Korean, preferably bilingual.</span></li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>UNOPND</company>
<location> United States California US</location>
<tags>business-development, sales, non-tech, blockchain, crypto, nft</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49691</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:06:27 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Technical Support Engineer - North America</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ETO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About The Role<br><br></strong>Zero Hash is looking for an experienced Technical Support Engineer, with a background in FinTech SAAS businesses, who is looking to build the infrastructure for Finance 2.0. You´ll be responsible for ensuring smooth technical operations across our client base and tech stack. You will be the public face of the company and interact directly with our partners.<br><br>This is a perfect role for someone who is looking for a fast-paced role in a hyper-growth company, with high reward.<br><br>Job Description:<br></p><ul> <li>Provide analysis and real time reporting for major incidents, SLAs, SLOs, etc. to key partners</li> <li>Support incident response on critical applications and infrastructure issues</li> <li>Ability to communicate technical issues to customers</li> <li>Triage and troubleshoot system issues</li> <li>Work closely with developers and operational teams on escalated technical issues</li> <li>Manage Zendesk and JIRA related workflows</li> <li>Create alerts and dashboards based on application logs and business metrics</li> <li>Strive for zero outages and a low level of production issues.<br><br> </li> </ul>Requirements:<br><ul> <li>Experience of technical operations </li> <li>Knowledge of relational/document-oriented databases incl. SQL</li> <li>Ability to perform REST API/FIX API troubleshooting</li> <li>Familiarity with Python/Bash scripting is a plus</li> <li>Basic understanding of a blockchain and trading environment is appreciated</li> <li>Customer focused mentality with attention to detail and accuracy</li> <li>Discipline in properly following up on all customer requests</li> <li>Experience with Zendesk, Jira, Confluence, and real-time monitoring tools such as grafana, prometheus, loki, opsgenie<br><br> </li> </ul>Benefits Offered<br><br>We believe that the best way to succeed is by having a happy, motivated and healthy team. We offer the following benefits:<br><ul> <li>Healthcare Insurance: Zero Hash covers roughly 100% of employee premiums as well as a portion of spouse/children</li> <li>Vision &amp; Dental Insurance</li> <li>Mental Health and Wellness Program</li> <li>Equity Ownership and Early Exercise</li> <li>Maternity &amp; Paternity Leave</li> <li>Educational budget of $1000</li> <li>WFH stipend of $500</li> <li>WeWork All Access Membership</li> <li>Visa Sponsorship</li> <li>401k<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>About Zero Hash<br><br></strong>Zero Hash is a B2B embedded infrastructure platform that allows any platform to integrate digital assets natively into their own customer experience quickly and easily (a matter of API endpoints). We power neo-banks, broker-dealers, and payment groups to offer digital asset trading and custody, crypto-backed rewards and round-ups programs as well as yield through staking and DeFi and NFTs.<br><br>Our thesis is very simple: every financial services firm will offer digital assets within the next 2 years and will do so through platforms such as Zero Hash. Zero Hash is defining the new FinTech vertical of digital-assets-as-a-service.<br><br>Clients include MoneyLion, Wirex, Deserve, MoonPay, tastytrade, Drivewealth. Backed by Point72 Ventures, NYCA, Bain Capital, tastytrade.<br><br>The Zero Hash Culture<br><br>All Zero Hash employees are guided by the following characteristics and core principles:<br><ul> <li>Independence/Ownership - An ability to work autonomously. Join Zero Hash, pitch ideas, and shape the work you do.</li> <li>Passion - We are innovating quickly and challenging the status quo. We want you to think big, be creative and make a difference every day.</li> <li>Collaborative - A good attitude and respect for others. We’re teammates, not co-workers. Everything we do is a shared success and equally a shared failure - we talk in terms of “we” not “me”.</li> <li>Initiative - An ability and passion for learning and asking questions. We will champion you, challenge you and push you to achieve your best - and we expect you to do the same.</li> <li>Empathy - An ability to listen, respect and understand your co-workers, customers and everyone you interact with no matter how different they are to you. We are proud of our diversity.</li> <li>Adaptability - An ability to respond quickly. We are in a fast-paced industry and so we expect you to be creative when solving a new problem and comfortable under pressure.</li> <li>Transparency - We believe that transparency is critical to empowering everyone to make the best decisions, both the company to its people and vice versa. Both as an organization and as individuals, we need to admit mistakes and learn from them.</li> <li>Integrity - Integrity creates trust. As both an organization collectively and as individuals, it is our most valuable asset.</li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Zero Hash</company>
<location> IL Chicago US</location>
<tags>dev, customer-support, blockchain, crypto, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49690</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:05:21 +0700</pubDate>
<title>QA Team Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ATO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>At Coinbase, our mission is to increase economic freedom around the world, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web3 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.<br>There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a culture like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our mission-focused approach to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.<br><strong>Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:</strong><br></p><ul> <li>You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there. </li> <li>You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0. </li> <li>You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.</li> <li>You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.</li> <li>You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.</li> <li>You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. </li> </ul><br>The QA lead will work as part of the Compliance Operations Quality Assurance team, which is responsible for conducting Quality Assurance audits on Transaction Monitoring alerts, US Investigations and Suspicious Activity Reports. You will be working with senior stakeholders from CX and Compliance. In your day-to-day role you will be responsible for cases allocations, procedural updates, creation and presentation of metrics, training of new analysts, conducting check and challenge reviews and working on providing a feedback loop on QA results and findings.<br><strong><u>What You’ll Be Doing (ie. Job Duties)</u></strong><br><ul> <li>Act as a directly responsible individual for the US Escalations Quality Assurance programme for CX</li> <li>Complete weekly allocations of cases to be audited by analysts</li> <li>Produce weekly metrics providing a detailed overview of the errors identified in audits and QA scores</li> <li>Present the QA results to senior stakeholders in weekly meetings</li> <li>Manage Critical Error Remediation validation process</li> <li>Act as a trusted point of contact for escalations and high priority issues related to your scope</li> <li>Review disputes and make the decision based on the existing documented process and regulatory requirements</li> <li>Implement new QA rubrics and frameworks </li> <li>Achieve service level agreements and quality metrics for your line of business, at the individual and team level</li> <li>Identify process gaps and work with stakeholders within CX and financial crime to improve the process</li> <li>Collaborate with internal support teams across Data Analytics, Escalations teams, Financial Crime Compliance, and L&amp;D to help launch or improve existing processes and workflow </li> <li>Utilize an in-depth understanding of metrics to drive data-driven recommendations </li> <li>Continuously add value through effective impact analysis, prioritization and efficient execution of projects.</li> </ul><br><strong><u>What We Look For In You (ie. Job Requirements)</u></strong><br><ul> <li>5+ Years hands-on experience in executing QA, Audit, or Compliance Testing programs across a diverse range of financial services/products</li> <li>Experience in working across multiple AML systems and programs simultaneously (e.g., experience in combinations of KYC, AML, and sanctions</li> <li>Working knowledge of BSA/AML laws, regulations, and rules for financial services/products</li> <li>Track record of delivering work outcome to budget and meeting quality standards</li> <li>Experience in assisting, developing, and producing metrics and reporting</li> <li>Strong written/verbal communication, critical thinking, and problem-solving skills</li> <li>Highly-motivated, analytical, organized, innovative, and adaptive</li> <li>Multi-tasking ability, team-oriented, and a self-starter</li> <li>Proven ability to work collaboratively with global partners in other functional units</li> <li>Exceptional work ethic and flexibility to work extended hours to meet deadlines, when necessary</li> <li>Ability to work with limited direction from management when situations occur</li> <li>Intermediate to advanced level in PowerPoint/Google Slides and Excel/Google Sheets </li> </ul><br><strong><u>Nice To Haves</u></strong><br><ul> <li>Vendor management experience</li> <li>Experience at crypto exchanges or in financial services, ideally in payments, trading operations or technical support.</li> <li>Experience in project management or analytics or quality assurance.</li> <li>Advanced degree in business, finance or legal </li> <li>Advanced understanding of Google apps, JIRA and Salesforce Service Cloud</li> </ul><br>Position ID - P34766<br>Pay Transparency Notice: Depending on your work location, the target annual salary for this position can range from $96,475 to $113,500 + target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).<br>Commitment to Equal Opportunity<br>Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law. For US applicants, you may view Pay Transparency, Employee Rights and Know Your Rights notices by clicking on their corresponding links. Additionally, Coinbase participates in the E-Verify program in certain locations, as required by law.<br>Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to accommodations[at]coinbase.com and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information. For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site click here to download a free compatible screen reader (free step by step tutorial can be found here).<br>Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants<br>Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available here. By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required. For US applicants only, by submitting your application you are agreeing to arbitration of disputes as outlined here. When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Coinbase</company>
<location> FL Miami US</location>
<tags>lead, quality-assurance, crypto, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49689</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:05:14 +0700</pubDate>
<title>DeFi Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kDO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>We are looking for someone to initiate, develop and execute foundational DeFi strategic initiatives for the Flow ecosystem to establish it as a key contender in the blockchain ecosystem. This is an entrepreneurial role and ideal candidate needs to demonstrate they have operated at the intersection of Product Management &amp; Business Development with a strong focus on financial &amp; liquidity principles.</p><br><p><strong>What We'll Accomplish Together</strong></p><br><ul> <li>Develop, lead &amp; execute the overall DeFi business strategy for Flow, including product development, partnerships, and business development.</li> <li>Increase the visibility of Flow within the TradFi and Mining/Staking community.</li> <li>Lead with the best security practice and standards. Ensure the steady growth and safe-run of their business from hacks and financial attacks.</li> <li>Provide expertise for Flow Foundation treasury management in partnership with the CFO.</li> <li>Monitor and analyze DeFi market trends, competitive landscape, and developer feedback to optimize our product offerings.</li> </ul><br><p><strong>A Litte About You:</strong></p><br><ul> <li>Bachelor's degree in finance, economics, or a related field.</li> <li>Strong understanding of DeFi protocols, smart contracts, and blockchain technology.</li> <li>Proven track record of launching and scaling successful DeFi products.</li> <li>Strong leadership and team management skills.</li> <li>Excellent communication, collaboration, and problem-solving skills.</li> <li>Ability to work in a fast-paced, dynamic environment and adapt to changes quickly.</li> <li>Passion for decentralization, blockchain technology, and financial inclusion.</li> </ul><br><p><strong>More about Flow:</strong></p><br><p>Flow is the layer 1 blockchain for builders. Flow blockchain is designed for a new generation of consumer apps, games, and the digital assets that power them. Flow helps developers build the kinds of applications people want to use, focusing on consumer-friendly onboarding and the ability to handle mainstream scale. The Flow team is a humble and curious bunch of builders, scientists, marketers and product experts who share a passion for blockchain technology and the new kinds of software it enables. Our people are our greatest strength: our diverse team flourishes in an environment where personal autonomy and professional growth are encouraged.</p><p></p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Flow Blockchain</company>
<location> United States US</location>
<tags>lead, blockchain, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49688</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:04:57 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Business Developer Executive (Blockchain)</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gDO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>We have a client in need of a business development executive. You will be joining oin a rapidly-growing organization, work independently without oversight, and help the company grow. This role requires the individual to be a self starter who excels working in a fast paced environment. This is an amazing career opportunity to help accelerate our growth within a remote-first, and rapidly-growing company.<br><br><strong><u>Responsibilities<br><br></u></strong>Build strong relationship with new clients while maintaining existing client relationships<br><br>Conduct sales presentations to a range of prospective clients<br><br>Build continuous pipeline of clients and projects<br><br>Identify new growth strategies while improving existing ones<br><br>Conduct market research<br><br>Collect and maintain client information within a CRM<br><br>Develop business plans, sales pitches, presentations, reference material, and other documents as required<br><br>Coordinate with various internal stakeholders and departments to optimize the sales effort<br><br><strong><u>Requirements<br><br></u></strong>Strong proven sales background<br><br>Strong communicator<br><br>Exceptional at building relationships both internally across the business and externally with clients and partners<br><br>Ability to work in a fast paced environment<br><br>Ability to work independently and remotely in a globally-distributed team without oversight<br><br>Proactive approach<br><br>Proven experience of working to tight deadlines<br><br>Experience negotiating a broad set of deals and contracts<br><br>Good high level understanding of<br><br>Blockchain and Web3 in general, for example, Ethereum ecosystem and DeFi<br><br>Experience working with the following -<br><br>Slack, Google Suite, CRMs, and other related platforms and tools<br><br><strong><u>Perks And Benefits<br><br></u></strong>Fully remote<br><br>Competitive rates<br><br>Flexible working hours<br><br>Plus equity If you don’t meet all the criteria for this role. Please join our talent pipeline and tell us about yourself so we can match you with employers who need your skills and experience.</p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>DApp360 Workforce</company>
<location> United States Florida US</location>
<tags>dev, executive, blockchain, defi, ethereum</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49687</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 11:03:59 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Senior DevOps Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=cDO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Structure Financial:<br><br></strong>Founded by MIT &amp; Jump Trading alumni; backed by Polychain Capital; Structure empowers anyone in the world to access quality financial markets with ease.<br><br>The Structure app replaces an antiquated financial system crippled by waste and opacity; we are repackaging legacy financial products that were designed for exclusivity and non-participation and transforming them into digital assets that are fit for a global public.<br><br>We are a global, remote-first team of engineers, designers, traders, and innovators of all kinds working together to build solutions for globally systemic financial systems. We value innovative ideas and encourage the audacity required to bring those ideas to life.<br><br>At Structure, you'll have an opportunity to invent industry-disrupting financial technology that will dramatically improve financial markets for decades to come. By joining us at this early stage, you will also have a significant influence on the design, direction, and vision of Structure. We're looking for motivated individuals who share a passion for financial markets and building world-changing technology.<br><br>The Software DevOps/SRE team is responsible for developing and delivering secure, scalable, highly-available services that support all of Structure's technology and services.<br><br><strong>Responsibilities:<br></strong></p><ul> <li>Identify projects required to improve availability and reduce operational expenses. </li> <li>Design and implement systems to safely enable Structure's continued data growth without incurring incremental operational overhead or loss of availability. </li> <li>Design and implement adjustments to the overall network and system infrastructure of our cloud services to improve security, flexibility and availability of the overall system. </li> <li>Diagnose and resolve performance issues in complex systems to ensure reliable user-facing performance of the overall system. </li> <li>Participate in a 24/7 on-call rotation, responsible for the stable and reliable operation of all cloud services. </li> <li>Perform postmortem analysis in response to operational incidents, analyzing system telemetry to drive continual improvement. </li> <li>Participate and contribute in architectural discussions, reviews, improvements and future projects</li> <li>Increase automation and environment agnostic infrastructure while keeping an eye on new tools and techniques when possible<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Required Experience:<br></strong><ul> <li>BA/BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience</li> <li>Experience operating a complex highly available system</li> <li>Experience with high volume services</li> <li>Experience with distributed systems</li> <li>Experience with Docker, Kubernetes, and AWS (Hashicorp Vault is useful)</li> <li>Strong understanding of configuration management</li> <li>Experience with environment agnostic, transportable applications and infrastructure</li> <li>Experience with complex deployments and data structures<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Preferred Experience (Not Required):<br></strong><ul> <li>Recent experience in the FinTech, blockchain, or digital assets industry</li> <li>Passionate about crypto, blockchain, and/or DeFi innovation</li> <li>A proponent of open-source software licenses</li> <li> While we are 100% remote, the target location for this position is within the Eastern and Central timezones of the US. <br><br> </li> </ul><strong>What We Offer:<br></strong><ul> <li>Cash: Competitive Performance-Based Salary + Merit Increase &amp; Spot Bonus Opportunities</li> <li>Equity: Generous Stock Option Packages for Performance</li> <li>Tokens: Genesis Block Token Allocations</li> <li>Time Off: Unlimited Paid Time Off</li> <li>Flexibility: Work from Anywhere, Agile Environment, and more!<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Are you curious what the app looks like? </strong>Check it out here! When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Structure Financial</company>
<location> NY New York US</location>
<tags>devops, dev, senior, aws, blockchain, crypto, docker, defi, kubernetes</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49680</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 07:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Senior Manager, Quantitative Trader</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ADO2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="single-job-content body3 block" id="tabpanel-0" aria-labelledby="tab-0" role="tabpanel"> <div class="content-intro"> <p><span>At Ripple, we’re building a world where value moves like information does today. It’s big, it’s bold, and we’re already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs. </span></p> <p><span>If you’re ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.</span></p> </div> <div> <p><span>Ripple is looking for a Quantitative Trader to support the Trading &amp; Markets team in Crypto and FX Trading, Liquidity and Quantitative analysis. The candidate will get a chance to contribute to the inner workings of one of Crypto’s foundational firms and see a team of traders and quants apply institutional trading techniques to an emerging market. You will also get a chance to build on your understanding of macro forces and what that means for asset prices, market microstructure, advanced statistical analysis and get an opportunity to meet some of the brightest minds in Crypto within the firm as well as at conferences.</span></p> <p><span><strong>THE WORK:</strong></span></p> <p><span>The ideal candidate will be hyper focused on detail, have an understanding of financial markets (both crypto and traditional markets) and have proficient data analysis skills. The ability to clearly present complex ideas, data and solutions is a highly valued skill within the Trading &amp; Markets team. We prefer a candidate that is proficient with Python for data analysis or another major data analysis language as that marries well with our internal technology stack.</span></p> <p> <strong>WHAT YOU’LL DO:</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>Manage market risk for the Trading Desk </span></li> <li><span>Manage external trading relationships necessary to gather intel and  - OTC desks, Market Makers, Custodians, Exchanges, Stablecoin Issuers etc. </span></li> <li><span>Support the Ripple Markets team in monitoring and drawing insights from  external crypto liquidity</span></li> <li><span>Design and optimize automated processes to assess and report to trading guidelines</span></li> <li><span>Enhance the team’s ability to access and use microstructure data</span></li> <li><span>Quarterback internal and external engineering resources to achieve the market’s team broader trading objective, including deployment of proof of concepts</span></li> <li><span>As required, monitor systematic execution of trades, positions and P&amp;L</span></li> <li><span>Conduct post trade analysis of trading strategies and algo performance</span></li> </ul> </div> <div> <p><strong>WHAT YOU'LL BRING: </strong></p> </div> <div> <ul> <li><span>Bachelor degree in preferably Mathematics / Statistics/ Computer Science/ Financial Engineering</span></li> <li><span>3 + years of quantitative trading experience or experience managing market risk</span></li> <li><span>Solid quantitative and analytical skills, and proficiency in back-testing/simulation</span></li> <li><span>Demonstrable passion in digital assets and knowledge of blockchain fundamentals and DeFi protocols</span></li> <li><span>Strong programming skills in Python, C++ or Java</span></li> <li><span>Ability to work autonomously and/or remotely in a distributed team</span></li> <li><span>Entrepreneurial mindset and adaptability to a dynamic environment</span></li> </ul> </div> <div class="content-conclusion"> <hr> <p><strong>WHO WE ARE:</strong></p> <p><span>Do Your Best Work</span></p> <ul> <li><span>The opportunity to build in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders</span></li> <li><span>A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact.  A professional development budget to support other modes of learning.</span></li> <li><span>Thrive in an environment where no matter what race, ethnicity, gender, origin, or culture they identify with, every employee is a respected, valued, and empowered part of the team.</span></li> <li><span>Ripple is Flexible First: you have the option to work from home, from our offices, or a combination of the two around our centers of gravity (15 global offices).</span></li> <li><span>Weekly all-company meeting - business updates and ask me anything &gt;</span></li> <li><span>We come together for moments that matter which include team offsites, team bonding activities, happy hours and more!</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Control of Your Finances</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Competitive salary, bonuses, and equity</span></li> <li><span>Competitive benefits that cover physical and mental healthcare, retirement, family forming, and family support</span></li> <li><span>Employee giving match</span></li> <li><span>Mobile phone stipend</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Care of Yourself</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Twice a quarter R&amp;R days so you can rest and recharge</span></li> <li><span>Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite &amp; virtual programming</span></li> <li><span>Generous vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it</span></li> <li><span>Industry-leading parental leave policies. Family planning benefits.</span></li> <li><span>Catered lunches, fully-stocked kitchens with premium snacks/beverages, and plenty of fun events</span></li> </ul> <p><span><em data-stringify-type="italic">Benefits listed above are for full-time employees.</em></span></p> <hr> <div><em>Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.</em></div> <div> </div> <div><em>Please find our UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice and our California Applicant Privacy Notice for reference.</em></div> </div> <p></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Ripple</company>
<location>London, UK</location>
<tags>quantitative, quantitative-trader, trader, senior, blockchain, crypto, defi, java</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49678</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 07:01:15 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Ethereum Tech Lead, Hardhat</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gzN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p></p><p>We’re looking for an experienced software engineer to join the team responsible for Hardhat - our flagship product (5.7k stars on GitHub). Hardhat is a development environment for Ethereum software. It consists of different components for editing, compiling, debugging, and deploying smart contracts and dApps, all working together to create a complete development environment.</p><p></p><p><strong>This is a fully-remote role, and we’re open to candidates applying within UTC-3 to UTC+4 timezones.</strong></p><p></p><h4>There are two challenges that we focus on:</h4><ol> <li><p>As Ethereum continues to evolve, we are dedicated to pushing the boundaries of what's possible and keeping Hardhat at the forefront of innovation and up-to-date.</p></li> <li><p>With Hardhat’s user base growing rapidly (70-100K MAU), we see every bug report and feature request as an opportunity to improve and deliver an exceptional experience. By staying on top of these challenges, we are constantly raising the bar for ourselves and inspiring others to do the same.</p></li> </ol><p>In this role, you'll have the opportunity to work closely with our Hardhat Team Lead to create cutting-edge functionality, eliminate bugs, and provide solutions for any issues that arise. You'll play a vital role in upholding our commitment to open-source software by actively contributing to the repository and collaborating with fellow developers, listening to feedback, and incorporating new ideas into our codebase, ensuring our software remains relevant and impactful. Through your efforts, you'll help us maintain our reputation for excellence and inspire others to join us in our mission.</p><p></p><h4><strong>The skills we look for:</strong></h4><ul> <li><p>Familiarity with the Ethereum ecosystem is required, as Hardhat is a key component of Ethereum developer tooling. Understanding how its different parts fit together is important for making sound technical decisions and tackling challenges effectively</p></li> <li><p>At least 5 years of experience as a software engineer</p></li> <li><p>Prior experience with dApp or Solidity development</p></li> <li><p>Knowledge and experience with Node.js and TypeScript</p></li> <li><p>We work remotely and mostly asynchronously, so the ability to take ownership and work with minimal direction is crucial</p></li> <li><p>Prior experience working in a remote and globally-distributed environment</p></li> </ul><p></p><h4><strong>Tech stack:</strong></h4><ul> <li><p>TypeScript</p></li> <li><p>Node.js</p></li> <li><p>Ethereum / EVM</p></li> <li><p>Solidity</p></li> <li><p>Ethers.js</p></li> </ul><p></p><h4><strong>The advantages you can attain from this opportunity:</strong></h4><ul> <li><p>You’ll have a chance to work on a core component of the Ethereum stack and support the entire Ethereum ecosystem to be more productive</p></li> <li><p>Contribute to Ethereum as a project</p></li> <li><p>Service the needs of high-profile projects that use Hardhat</p></li> <li><p>All of your work will be open-source, and you’ll have the chance to collaborate with other open-source projects (both inside and outside Ethereum)</p></li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Nomic Foundation</company>
<location> Berlin Berlin Germany</location>
<tags>hardhat, lead, tech-lead, ethereum, remote, dapp, node, solidity</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49677</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 07:00:50 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Software Engineer, Games</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=czN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p></p><h4>Who We Are</h4><p>The Solana Foundation is dedicated to the adoption, decentralization, and security of the Solana network. Our mission is to help support and grow the Solana network and its community while driving mass adoption for blockchain. The Solana Foundation is working to realize a world where individuals own their data, use permissionless networks, and transfer information freely around the world.</p><p></p><h4>What We Do</h4><p>The Ecosystem Engineering team is a horizontal team of strategically deployed engineers that live at the intersection of business, technology, and innovation in the Solana ecosystem. We support teams small and large by providing technical guidance, architecture review, and maximize our leverage by driving adoption of technical public goods through code and coordination.</p><p>Like developing games? How about hundreds of games? Game studios from the biggest to the smallest are making great games on Solana, and this role is here to facilitate that development. If you’re looking to join a fast paced, problem solving environment at the center of blockchain infrastructure, cryptocurrency, and great gaming experiences, then read on!</p><p></p><h4>To be successful in this role</h4><p>You will:</p><ul> <li><p>Develop, maintain, and support open source tooling and SDKs for popular game engines such as Unity and Unreal</p></li> <li><p>Main focuses are on account management, inventory database integrations, interoperability. These will be open source tools, guides, and templates that will enables games and game service providers to interface with Solana </p></li> <li><p>Interact effectively with other team members and game studios building on the Solana network.</p></li> </ul><p>You ideally have: </p><ul> <li><p>3+ years of experience in game development in Unity and/or Unreal</p></li> <li><p>Experience managing gaming database connections, game tools, building APIs / SDKs</p></li> <li><p>The ability to write scripts to improve monitoring and automation</p></li> <li><p>A special interest in making fun games that happen to use blockchain technologies (a ton of them!) </p></li> <li><p>C# or C++ expertise (pref both)</p></li> </ul><p>Bonus points:</p><ul> <li><p>Familiarity with Rust / JavaScript / TypeScript (especially in the context of the Solana core protocol and RPC)</p></li> <li><p>Experience with smart contract-enabled blockchains like Solana, Ethereum, or Cosmos</p></li> <li><p>Experience as an open source contributor</p></li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Solana Foundation</company>
<location> Remote Remote USA</location>
<tags>dev, remote, blockchain, ethereum, javascript, rust, solana, typescript</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49674</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 4 May 2023 02:41:27 +0700</pubDate>
<title>General Compliance Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QzN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="single-job-content body3 block" id="tabpanel-0" aria-labelledby="tab-0" role="tabpanel"> <div class="content-intro"> <p><span>At Ripple, we’re building a world where value moves like information does today. It’s big, it’s bold, and we’re already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs. </span></p> <p><span>If you’re ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.</span></p> </div> <div> <p><strong>THE WORK:</strong></p> <p><span>Ripple is seeking to hire an experienced Manager to support all aspects of its Global General Compliance program. This position will be heavily focused on supporting the day-to-day operations of the General Compliance team. This position reports to the Senior Manager, General Compliance. </span></p> <p><strong>WHAT YOU’LL DO:</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>Manage day-to-day activities of Ripple’s General Compliance team, including but not limited to, managing the Vendor Risk Management Program, supporting Ripple’s Business Continuity Program, and working with global compliance leads to execute and maintain program requirements.</span></li> <li><span>Assist with the review, updates and improvement of compliance policies, procedures, training and awareness to drive compliant behavior.</span></li> <li><span>Generate and maintain appropriate records and metrics related to the Reporting Hotline.</span></li> <li><span>Perform periodic evaluation of program controls and recommend solutions for identified areas of improvement.</span></li> <li><span>Work cross functionally (Product, Engineering, Customer Success, Finance, People Operations, Legal) to update business continuity program documents and maintain business continuity and disaster recovery testing schedule and testing evidence. </span></li> <li><span>Coordinate with all teams to perform vendor assessments, due diligence, and report on vendor risks throughout the vendor’s lifecycle.</span></li> <li><span>Prepare ad-hoc and quarterly reports, presentation slides, and program material for employees, subsidiaries and senior leadership.</span></li> </ul> </div> <div> <p><strong>WHAT YOU'LL BRING: </strong></p> </div> <div> <ul> <li><span>Bachelors and/or Master’s Degree from an accredited university or college</span></li> <li><span>6+ years of relevant compliance experience</span></li> <li><span>Strong knowledge of Corporate Compliance subjects, business processes, internal control structures, and risk management</span></li> <li><span>Strong communication (presentation, writing, speaking) and interpersonal skills, with an attention to detail and a commitment to excellence</span></li> <li><span>Experience developing process maps and tools for effective compliance monitoring</span></li> <li><span>Comfortable executing independently in a team environment with minimal supervision</span></li> <li><span>Comfortable working in a fast-paced environment</span></li> <li><span>Previous experience preferred in business continuity planning, disaster recovery, and/or vendor management</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Other common names for this role: </span></p> </div> <div class="content-conclusion"> <hr> <p><strong>WHO WE ARE:</strong></p> <p><span>Do Your Best Work</span></p> <ul> <li><span>The opportunity to build in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders</span></li> <li><span>A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact.  A professional development budget to support other modes of learning.</span></li> <li><span>Thrive in an environment where no matter what race, ethnicity, gender, origin, or culture they identify with, every employee is a respected, valued, and empowered part of the team.</span></li> <li><span>Ripple is Flexible First: you have the option to work from home, from our offices, or a combination of the two around our centers of gravity (15 global offices).</span></li> <li><span>Weekly all-company meeting - business updates and ask me anything &gt;</span></li> <li><span>We come together for moments that matter which include team offsites, team bonding activities, happy hours and more!</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Control of Your Finances</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Competitive salary, bonuses, and equity</span></li> <li><span>Competitive benefits that cover physical and mental healthcare, retirement, family forming, and family support</span></li> <li><span>Employee giving match</span></li> <li><span>Mobile phone stipend</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Care of Yourself</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Twice a quarter R&amp;R days so you can rest and recharge</span></li> <li><span>Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite &amp; virtual programming</span></li> <li><span>Generous vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it</span></li> <li><span>Industry-leading parental leave policies. Family planning benefits.</span></li> <li><span>Catered lunches, fully-stocked kitchens with premium snacks/beverages, and plenty of fun events</span></li> </ul> <p><span><em data-stringify-type="italic">Benefits listed above are for full-time employees.</em></span></p> <hr> <div><em>Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.</em></div> <div> </div> <div><em>Please find our UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice and our California Applicant Privacy Notice for reference.</em></div> </div> <p></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Ripple</company>
<location>London, UK</location>
<tags>compliance, non-tech, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49668</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 23:10:14 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Business Operation Generalist</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gjN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Job Position: Business Operation Generalist<br>Location: Texas, US (Remote Acceptable)<br>Company: https://infstones.com/<br>Contact: recruiter-usa@infstones.com<br><strong>About Company</strong><br>InfStones is an advanced, enterprise-grade Platform as a Service (PaaS) blockchain infrastructure provider trusted by the top blockchain companies in the world. InfStones’ AI-based infrastructure provides developers worldwide with a rugged, powerful node management platform alongside an easy-to-use API. With over 15,000 nodes supported on over 60 blockchains, InfStones gives developers all the control they need - reliability, speed, efficiency, security, and scalability - for cross-chain DeFi, NFT, GameFi, and decentralized application development. InfStones is trusted by the biggest blockchain companies in the world including Binance, CoinList, BitGo, OKX, Chainlink, Polygon, Harmony, and KuCoin, among a hundred other customers. InfStones is dedicated to developing the next evolution of a better world through limitless Web3 innovation.<br>To date, InfStones has raised over $110 million in capital and is backed by Softbank, GGV Capital, Susquehanna International Group (SIG), Dragonfly Capital, Qiming Venture Partners, Plug and Play and many renowned institutional investors. InfStones is proud to offer medical, vision, dental, short-term and long-term disability insurance, 401(k) plan with company matching, FSA, and other benefits to all full-time employees, along with flexible paid time off, sick day, and holidays.<br>The Role<br>You will be helping connect the entire blockchain industry by onboarding companies and developers to our infrastructure to expedite their product development. You’ll be leading the charge at one of the most cutting-edge companies, with incredible growth, in the industry. You will be responsible for owning the customer onboarding stages of the sales/business development process.<br><strong>Job Description</strong><br></p><ul> <li> Be the expert on our staking and infrastructure products. Educate customers about staking economics, blockchain infrastructure, and how to utilize our platform</li> <li> Collaborate across business, product, marketing, and engineering teams to drive the desired business outcomes for our customers</li> <li> Contact, prospect, and qualify potential customers and partners through inbound and outbound sales efforts and campaigns</li> <li> Own, manage, and report using CRM systems: ensure the system is up to date and that all relevant metrics are recorded<br> </li> </ul><br><strong>Qualifications</strong><br><ul> <li> B.S. in Computer Science / Economics / Finance, or other Business related fields</li> <li> 2+ years’ experience with inbound, outbound, and client-facing requests, positioning SaaS, or PaaS offerings</li> <li> Knowledge and passion for the crypto/blockchain industry</li> <li> Naturally curious and an eagerness to learn new technologies</li> <li> Excellent listening, verbal and written communication skills</li> <li> Basic data analytics skills and able to utilize relevant tools effectively to present insights</li> <li> Self-starter attitude and the ability to research new ideas with autonomy<br> </li> </ul><br><strong>Preferred Qualifications (Nice To Have)</strong><br><ul> <li> Relevant experience in Web 3.0/Blockchain industry</li> <li> Relevant experience in start-ups</li> <li> Experience with Agile management tools, and CRM software including the configuration, and development of dashboards and reports<br><br> </li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>InfStones</company>
<location> United States Texas US</location>
<tags>blockchain, crypto, defi, nft, node</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49665</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 21:40:48 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Partner Marketing Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=UjN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<section id="job-openings" class="job-openings"> <div class="container"> <div class="content-intro"><p><em>Founded in 2018 and already valued at over $8 billion, Fireblocks is a SaaS platform that helps companies to create innovative products on the blockchain and manage day-to-day crypto operations. Fireblocks is trusted by some of the largest financial institutions, banks, globally-recognized brands, and Web3 companies in the world, including BNY Mellon, BNP Paribas, ANZ Bank, Revolut, and thousands more, to securely scale digital asset operations through the Fireblocks Network and MPC-based wallet infrastructure. We have offices in New York, London, Tel Aviv, and Singapore, and we are continuing to expand our teams to reach new customers globally.</em></p></div> <h4>What you'll do</h4> <p><span>Fireblocks is looking for a seasoned Partner Marketing Manager to own the organization’s partner marketing strategy and execution which will drive towards the company’s business objectives, as well as address the needs and interests of our customers and prospects. The position’s main duties include creating a partner marketing strategy, executing on that strategy to deliver on the pipeline and revenue objectives of Fireblocks. </span></p> <h4>Responsibilities</h4> <ul> <li><span>Deliver quarterly marketing KPIs related to Fireblocks’ partners - leads, marketing qualified leads, pipeline, and win revenue</span></li> <li><span>Manage tactical execution of marketing programs which build pipeline and eminence for partner programs and drive business growth for Fireblocks’ partnerships go to market initiatives</span></li> <li><span>Support the development of strategic messaging and positioning to differentiate Fireblocks and advance awareness of partner capabilities, offerings, solutions, and successes across the broader organization and in the marketplace</span></li> <li><span>Create integrated marketing campaigns to differentiate Fireblocks. This includes creating collaborating with internal resources to produce marketing content, and producing material suites over various channels (digital, print, social, video, etc.) to aid with local activation in targeted geographies</span></li> <li><span>Track, monitor, measure and report on the effectiveness of partner marketing activities.</span></li> <li><span>Produce deliverables including, thought leadership (whitepapers, reports, surveys, etc.), Fireblocks-hosted and third-party events, externally facing videos and webcasts, speaking opportunities for partner leaders, social media and blogging, and digital advertising.</span></li> <li><span>Coordinate and collaborate with a cross-functional marketing team to get projects completed and successfully promoted.</span></li> <li><span>Collaborate with country-based marketing professionals to ensure alliances are positioned consistently.</span></li> <li><span>Strong project management skills for managing cross-functional projects</span></li> <li><span>Ability to engage effectively in cross-cultural initiatives and engagements across multiple time zones</span></li> <li><span>Excellent communications (written, PowerPoint, and verbal), especially for communicating and presenting to senior-level executives</span></li> <li><span>Self-motivated, work independently and can proactively resolve issues and make process improvements</span></li> <li><span>Team player mentality and positive, "can do" attitude</span></li> <li><span>Ability to work in a fast-paced environment</span></li> <li><span>Ability to synthesize information to create succinct materials; familiarity with integrating various technologies and tools to support marketing efforts</span></li> <li><span>Strong written and oral communications skills</span></li> <li><span>Strong negotiation, project management and problem-solving skills; flexibility and adaptability</span></li> <li><span>Demonstrable project management skills and ability to prioritize multiple tasks simultaneously</span></li> </ul> <h4>Minimum Requirements</h4> <ul> <li><span>5-8 years of B2B marketing</span></li> <li><span>Bachelor’s degree (preferably in marketing/communications/business)</span></li> <li><span>Ability to travel 10%</span></li> </ul> <h4>Preferred Qualifications</h4> <ul> <li><span>Knowledge of and past marketing experience with SaaS companies</span></li> <li><span>Knowledge of and experience in crypto and digital assets</span></li> <li><span>Partner relationship management experience (i.e., alliance partners, channel marketing partners) with both start-ups and enterprise companies</span></li> <li><span>Proven experience across a broad range of marketing activities, disciplines, and tactics. (e.g., demand gen and content creation aligned to a target audience buyer’s journey, channel marketing, field marketing, etc.)</span></li> </ul> <p><em>We’d love for you to have financial services, fintech, blockchain, cybersecurity or crypto industry experience but it is not a requirement. We have a comprehensive onboarding and training program for all new employees.</em></p> <p><em>For employees hired to work remotely from New York, or from our NYC HQ, Fireblocks is required by law to include a reasonable estimate of the compensation range for this role. This range is specific to New York City, and takes into consideration a wide range of factors that are reviewed when making a hiring decision, such as years of experience, skills, and other business needs.</em></p> <p><em>It is not typical for a candidate to be hired at or near the top of the pay range and each compensation decision is dependent on each individual case. A reasonable base salary range estimate for this position is $94,000 - $136,000 The base salary is one component of the total compensation package, which for some roles may include a target bonus, a very competitive equity grant, and very generous benefits. </em></p> <p><em>While we believe competitive compensation is a critical aspect of you deciding to join us, we do hope you also spend time considering why our mission and culture are right for you. We are creating something transformational here, and we hope you are as excited about the future as we are.</em></p> <p> </p> <div class="content-conclusion"> <p><em>Fireblocks' mission is to enable every business to easily and securely access digital assets and cryptocurrencies. In order to do that, we strongly believe our workforce should be as diverse as our clients, and this is why we embrace diversity and inclusion in all its forms. </em></p> <h6><em>Please see our candidate privacy policy here.</em></h6> </div> <div id="grnhse_app"></div> </div> </section> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Fireblocks</company>
<location>Location: New York</location>
<tags>marketing-manager, marketing, non-tech, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49660</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 18:24:31 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Web Developer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=AjN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>Responsibilities:</p> <ul> <li>Develop new web apps</li> <li>Maintain and improve existing sites like blueskyweb.xyz and atproto.com</li> </ul> <p>You might be a good fit if you:</p> <ul> <li>Have 4+ years of experience with Javascript and React</li> <li>Deeply understand HTML, CSS, and web technologies</li> <li>Understand responsive design, mobile-first, and PWAs </li> <li>Have "an eye for design", even if you're not a designer</li> <li>Have ideas about what the future of social could look like</li> <li>Can use mockup and UI prototyping tools to express your ideas</li> <li>Like working on small, fast-moving teams </li> <li>Like learning and building new things</li> <li>Love finding that moment when users are delighted</li> </ul> <p>We're a fully remote team, though an overlap of working hours with CST is required. For full-time roles we offer health, dental, and vision insurance.<br><br>Bluesky’s mission is to transition the social web from platforms to protocols. We’re building a federated social network where users have more power. Our team has decades of combined experience building distributed applications. As a web developer, you’ll show users new ways of using social media that they didn’t know were possible.</p> <p>To apply, email with:</p> <ul> <li>A resume or CV (link or PDF)</li> <li>A cover letter that tells us why you care about this problem and how your skills equip you to work on it (link or PDF)</li> <li>A link to your GitHub, GitLab, or a portfolio of past work</li> </ul> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Bluesky</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>dev, css, front-end, javascript, react, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49659</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 18:22:47 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Typescript Developer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kTN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>Responsibilities:</p> <ul> <li>Develop and maintain the Typescript AT Protocol implementation</li> <li>Scale our existing services to millions of users</li> <li>Create SDK and API tools for an ecosystem of protocol developers</li> </ul> <p>You might be a good fit if you:</p> <ul> <li>Have 4+ years of experience with Typescript</li> <li>Have a strong knowledge of data structures and software design principles</li> <li>Have experience working with Postgres at scale</li> <li>Are familiar with distributed systems</li> <li>Have built scalable and high-performance server-side applications</li> <li>Like working on small, fast-moving teams</li> <li>Read the atproto docs and want to contribute</li> </ul> <p>We’re especially excited if you have:</p> <ul> <li>Previous experience working on social sites</li> <li>Experience with cryptographic primitives such as public/private keys and merkle trees</li> <li>Experience with the IPLD or DID ecosystems</li> <li>Experience with Golang or React</li> </ul> <p>We're a fully remote team, though an overlap of working hours with CST (Central Standard Time) is required. For full-time roles we offer health, dental, and vision insurance.<br><br>Bluesky’s mission is to transition the social web from platforms to protocols. We’re building a federated social network where users have more power. Our team has decades of combined experience building distributed applications. As a Typescript dev, you’ll be writing protocol and backend code that will be a critical part of transforming social media.</p> <p>To apply, email with:</p> <ul> <li>A resume or CV (link or PDF)</li> <li>A cover letter that tells us why you care and how you can contribute (link or PDF)</li> <li>A link to your GitHub, GitLab, or a portfolio of past work</li> </ul> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Bluesky</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>typescript, dev, api, backend, javascript, node, postgres, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49658</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 18:21:04 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Mobile Developer (React Native)</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gTN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>Responsibilities:</p> <ul><li>Prototype, develop, and ship mobile apps</li></ul> <p>You might be a good fit if you:</p> <ul> <li>Have 4+ years of experience using React Native</li> <li>Can write clean, reusable code</li> <li>Are confident building animations, gestures, and UI state managers</li> <li>Care about that last 10% that makes apps feel <em>nice</em> </li> <li>Have ideas about what the future of social could look like</li> <li>Can use mockup and UI prototyping tools to express your ideas</li> <li>Like working on small, fast-moving teams</li> <li>Like learning and building new things</li> <li>Love finding that moment when users are delighted</li> </ul> <p><br>Bluesky’s mission is to transition the social web from platforms to protocols. We’re building a federated social network where users have more power. Our team has decades of combined experience building distributed applications. As a mobile developer, you’ll show users new ways of using social media that they didn’t know were possible.<br><br></p> <p>We’re a fully remote team, though an overlap of working hours with CST is required. For full-time roles we offer health, dental, and vision insurance.</p> <p>To apply, email with:</p> <ul> <li>A resume or CV (link or PDF)</li> <li>A cover letter that tells us why you care about this problem and how your skills equip you to work on it (link or PDF)</li> <li>A link to your GitHub, GitLab, or a portfolio of past work</li> </ul> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Bluesky</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>dev, mobile, javascript, react-native, remote, react</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49657</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 18:19:07 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Go Software Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=cTN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>Responsibilities:</p> <ul> <li>Design, develop, and maintain high-performance backend infrastructure</li> <li>Ship new features and enhancements</li> <li>Optimize existing systems for scalability, reliability, and performance</li> </ul> <p>You might be a good fit if you have:</p> <ul> <li>4+ years of experience with Go and backend systems</li> <li>Strong knowledge of data structures and software design principles</li> <li>Proven experience in building scalable and high-performance indexing systems, preferably for social media platforms or similar large-scale applications</li> <li>Familiarity with distributed systems, message queues, and microservice architectures</li> <li>Experience with networking, filesystems, and databases</li> <li>Experience working on large-scale systems</li> <li>Understanding of indexing and querying techniques</li> <li>Can work well independently, as well as on a team</li> <li>Like working on small, fast-moving teams</li> <li>Like learning and building new things</li> </ul> <p>We’re especially excited if you have:</p> <ul> <li>Experience working on social media platforms or similar high-traffic applications</li> <li>Have a copy of "Designing Data-Intensive Applications" and want to chat with the author</li> </ul> <p>We’re a fully remote team, though an overlap of working hours with USA Pacific Time (PST) is required. For full-time roles we offer health, dental, and vision insurance.</p> <p><br>Bluesky’s mission is to transition the social web from platforms to protocols. We’re building a federated social network where users have more power. Our team has decades of combined experience building distributed applications. Join us in building new forms of user-controlled social media.<br><br>To apply, email with:</p> <ul> <li>A resume or CV (link or PDF)</li> <li>A cover letter that tells us why you care about this problem and how your skills equip you to work on it (link or PDF)</li> <li>A link to your GitHub, GitLab, or a portfolio of past work</li> </ul> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Bluesky</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>dev, golang, backend, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49644</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:11:28 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Internal Communications and Operations Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QDN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Company Description<br><br></strong>It all started with an idea at Block in 2013. Initially built to take the pain out of peer-to-peer payments, Cash App has gone from a simple product with a single purpose to a dynamic ecosystem, developing unique financial products, including Afterpay/Clearpay, to provide a better way to send, spend, invest, borrow and save to our 47 million monthly active customers. We want to redefine the world’s relationship with money to make it more relatable, instantly available, and universally accessible.<br><br>Today, Cash App has thousands of employees working globally across office and remote locations, with a culture geared toward innovation, collaboration and impact. We’ve been a distributed team since day one, and many of our roles can be done remotely from the countries where Cash App operates. No matter the location, we tailor our experience to ensure our employees are creative, productive, and happy.<br><br>Check out our locations, benefits, and more at cash.app/careers.<br><br><strong>Job Description<br><br></strong>Cash App is seeking an Internal Communications and Operations Manager with exceptional project management skills to join our growing team. Reporting directly to the Head of Internal Communications, the successful candidate will serve as a trusted advisor to key business leaders and will be responsible for developing programs and playbooks to scale strategic business, organizational and leadership communications across the business.<br><br><strong>About our team: </strong>Cash App’s Internal Communications team acts as strategic advisors across the business to ensure relevant information gets to the right people in the right place at the right time. We aim to Inform, engage, and enable a globally distributed workforce, connecting Cash App team members with the tools, information, and resources they need to succeed.<br><br><strong>You will:<br></strong></p><ul> <li>Develop and implement a business communications strategy that enables operational leaders to regularly communicate strategic updates to employees </li> <li>Work with the Cash App leadership team to develop communications content and programming that supports Cash App operating principles, mission, vision, strategy and priorities </li> <li>Act as a cross-functional liaison between teams from various disciplines (eg. product, marketing, design) to ensure consistent messaging and communication</li> <li>Cyclical communications updates: partner with subject matter experts to develop an approach to curating and communicating quarterly business, organizational and financial updates</li> <li>Lead Project management for strategic initiatives driving operational excellence, developing playbooks and guidelines to support engagement and adoption of new platforms, processes or projects</li> <li>Develop internal communications briefs and updates that can scale for a growing business</li> <li>Manage projects from start to finish, including scoping, budgeting, and scheduling</li> <li>Collaborate with stakeholders to understand their needs and provide effective communications solutions</li> <li>Stay up-to-date with industry trends and best practices in internal communications<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Qualifications<br></strong><ul> <li>8+ years in communications, marketing, or related fields</li> <li>5+ years of experience in corporate communications, preferably in the tech industry</li> <li>Experience working with senior leadership, proactively identifying risks, opportunities, and areas for improvement, and providing guidance and support as needed</li> <li>Strong problem-solving skills and ability to apply a structured approach to tackle business challenges, identify root causes, and develop and execute effective solutions</li> <li>Excellent communication skills, including the ability to write and present complex concepts and ideas clearly and concisely to stakeholders at all levels of the organization</li> <li>Project Management expertise with the ability to develop project plans, manage team deadlines and goals</li> <li>Experience with project management and collaboration tools like Asana, Airtable, and Notion</li> <li>Proficient in Google Suite</li> <li>Ability to deal with ambiguity, work independently and manage multiple projects simultaneously<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Additional Information<br><br></strong>Block takes a market-based approach to pay, and pay may vary depending on your location. U.S. locations are categorized into one of four zones based on a cost of labor index for that geographic area. The successful candidate’s starting pay will be determined based on job-related skills, experience, qualifications, work location, and market conditions. These ranges may be modified in the future.<br><br>Zone A: USD $167,300 - USD $204,500<br><br>Zone B: USD $155,600 - USD $190,200<br><br>Zone C: USD $147,200 - USD $180,000<br><br>Zone D: USD $138,900 - USD $169,700<br><br>To find a location’s zone designation, please refer to this resource. If a location of interest is not listed, please speak with a recruiter for additional information.<br><br>Benefits include the following:<br><ul> <li>Healthcare coverage</li> <li>Retirement Plans including company match </li> <li>Employee Stock Purchase Program</li> <li>Wellness programs, including access to mental health, 1:1 financial planners, and a monthly wellness allowance </li> <li>Paid parental and caregiving leave</li> <li>Paid time off</li> <li>Learning and Development resources</li> <li>Paid Life insurance, AD&amp;D. and disability benefits </li> <li>Perks such as WFH reimbursements and free access to caregiving, legal, and discounted resources <br><br> </li> </ul>This role is also eligible to participate in Block's equity plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies, and may be eligible for a sign-on bonus. Sales roles may be eligible to participate in a commission plan subject to the terms of the applicable plans and policies. Pay and benefits are subject to change at any time, consistent with the terms of any applicable compensation or benefit plans.<br><br><strong>US and Canada EEOC Statement<br><br></strong>We’re working to build a more inclusive economy where our customers have equal access to opportunity, and we strive to live by these same values in building our workplace. Block is a proud equal opportunity employer. We work hard to evaluate all employees and job applicants consistently, without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, disability, pregnancy, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other legally protected class.<br><br>We believe in being fair, and are committed to an inclusive interview experience, including providing reasonable accommodations to disabled applicants throughout the recruitment process. We encourage applicants to share any needed accommodations with their recruiter, who will treat these requests as confidentially as possible. <strong><em>Want to learn more about what we’re doing to build a workplace that is fair and square? Check out our</em></strong><strong><em><u> I+D page</u></em></strong><strong><em>.<br><br></em></strong>Additionally, we consider qualified applicants with criminal histories for employment on our team, and always assess candidates on an individualized basis.<br><br><em>Block, Inc. (NYSE: SQ) is a global technology company with a focus on financial services. Made up of Square, Cash App, Spiral, TIDAL, and TBD, we build tools to help more people access the economy. Square helps sellers run and grow their businesses with its integrated ecosystem of commerce solutions, business software, and banking services. With Cash App, anyone can easily send, spend, or invest their money in stocks or Bitcoin. Spiral (formerly Square Crypto) builds and funds free, open-source Bitcoin projects. Artists use TIDAL to help them succeed as entrepreneurs and connect more deeply with fans. TBD is building an open developer platform to make it easier to access Bitcoin and other blockchain technologies without having to go through an institution.</em> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Cash App</company>
<location> NY New York US</location>
<tags>pr, non-tech, operations, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49643</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:11:19 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Personal Assistant</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MDN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>CoinFlip is a leading fintech company powered by cryptocurrency. Believing everyone deserves to participate in the new digital economy, the company operates one of the world’s largest networks of cryptocurrency ATMs — with over 4,000 active kiosks — as well as an over-the-counter trading desk. In 2022, CoinFlip became an international company by expanding into Canada , and launched CoinFlip Ventures , a new initiative designed to support start-up companies.<br>CoinFlip placed No. 60 on the 2021 Inc. 5000 list of the nation’s fastest-growing private companies. CoinFlip was also named the 2021 and 2022 #1 fastest-growing company in Chicago by Crain’s Business.<br>As our growth trajectory continues, we’re looking to quickly expand all of our teams. It’s an exciting time to join CoinFlip as we’re pursuing additional business lines and continued international expansion to further cement us as a leading financial technology company.<br>We’re seeking a Personal Assistant to perform personalized tasks. In this role you will be responsible for handling all personal out of office duties on behalf of our founder. You will be expected to make travel arrangements and assist with office duties when required.<br><strong><u>Responsibilities</u></strong><br></p><ul> <li>Reporting to our CEO and performing personal and at times administrative duties</li> <li>Handling and managing out of office documents/records</li> <li>Liaising with leadership team, answering calls, and making travel arrangements</li> <li>Managing internal and external correspondence on behalf of our founder</li> <li>Scheduling out of office appointments, maintaining personal events calendar, and sending reminders</li> <li>Copying, scanning, and faxing documents, as well as taking notes</li> <li>Preparing facilities for scheduled events and arranging refreshments, if required</li> <li>Ordering personal supplies and replacements, as well as managing mail and courier services</li> <li>Observing best personal/business practices and etiquette </li> <li>Other duties as assigned</li> </ul><br><strong><u>What We're Looking For In a Candidate</u></strong><br><ul> <li>Written and verbal communication skills</li> <li>Exceptional interpersonal skills</li> <li>Reporting skills</li> <li>Supply management</li> <li>Scheduling</li> <li>Computer software skills including Microsoft Office and G-Suite</li> <li>Organization skills</li> <li>Time management skills</li> <li>Presentation skills</li> <li>Office equipment maintenance</li> <li>Travel logistics</li> </ul><br><strong><u>The Nice To Have's</u></strong><br><ul> <li>Experience working for a rapidly growing startup, and managing change </li> <li>Experience in financial services, fintech and/or crypto </li> <li>5+ years of experience as a personal assistant would be advantageous</li> </ul><br><strong><u>Internal Referral</u></strong><br><ul><li>Tier One</li></ul><br>Working at CoinFlip means collaborating with experienced and innovative leaders who share a clear vision and a track record of success. We offer a collaborative and positive working environment where we encourage employees to balance productivity with time to recharge. Compensation is above and beyond a typical “startup” — we offer competitive salaries, performance-based incentives, and competitive benefits for full-time employees.<br>CoinFlip values diversity in the workplace and is an equal opportunity employer committed to providing an inclusive and accessible work environment. We thank all candidates who apply, but only those selected for an interview will be contacted.<br>By applying to this role, you give express consent to CoinFlip to send you informational text (SMS) messages regarding this role and the application process. You can cancel the SMS service at any time by replying "STOP" to the text message you received. If at any time you forget what keywords are supported, just reply "HELP." Message and data rates apply. If you require a special accommodation, please let us know and we’ll work with you to meet your needs. When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Olliv By CoinFlip</company>
<location> IL Chicago US</location>
<tags>virtual-assistant, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49642</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:10:59 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Crypto Hedge Fund Trader</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=IDN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Role: </strong>Crypto Hedge Fund Trader<br><br><strong>Location: </strong>Remote<br><br><strong>Duration: </strong>FTE/Permanent<br><br><strong><u>More Details<br></u></strong></p><ul> <li>Develop trading strategies which outperform Bitcoin</li> <li>Identify valuable and predictive data sources</li> <li>Build unique indicators and metrics to drive investment decisions and signals</li> <li>Skilled in investment risk-reward decision making<br> </li> </ul><strong><u>Requirements<br></u></strong><ul> <li>At least 2 years of experience working as a trader or doing quantitative research at a well respected fund or research firm</li> <li>A mathematical back-ground either through education (degree in Maths, Statistics, Data Science, or another Science related subject) or equivalent past experience</li> <li>Track record of profitability (could be a realistic backtest, algorithmic or manual live-trading track record)</li> <li>Data modeling skills (experience in Python or other data science language)</li> <li>Expertise in finding, integrating, optimizing and analyzing new datasets</li> <li>Quantitative mindset</li> <li>Creativity in coming up with new trading ideas and approaches</li> <li>Expertise in trading Bitcoin, altcoins and/or other crypto assets in a professional fashion</li> <li>Experience in working in a research and trading oriented team</li> <li>Systematic approach and attention to detail</li> </ul> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>VIR Consultant LLC</company>
<location> United States US</location>
<tags>trader, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49641</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:10:32 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Head of Marketing - Blockchain</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=EDN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>Head of Marketing - Blockchain/Crypto<br><br><strong>Company Overview<br><br></strong>Designed for the next generation of blockchain, the Oasis Network is the first privacy-enabled blockchain platform for Web3, a responsible data economy and a decentralized society. The Oasis Protocol Foundation supports projects focused on building privacy-preserving applications on top of the Oasis Network.<br><br><strong>Role Description<br><br></strong>The Oasis Protocol Foundation is looking for a Head of Marketing or Director of Marketing to lead in growing our ecosystem and generate awareness. The ideal candidate will demonstrate passion for the blockchain industry and will have excellent communication skills.<br><br><strong>Responsibilities<br></strong></p><ul> <li>Manage and lead the Marketing team</li> <li>Lead all marketing efforts including growth marketing, partnerships, product marketing, content, social media, data analytics, branding, PR and communications</li> <li>Develop quarterly OKRs and KPIs for the Marketing team</li> <li>Lead growth marketing strategy, dev acquisition, retention and engagement</li> <li>Structure and launch new programs, events, campaigns, and initiatives focused on growth marketing and branding</li> <li>Work closely with leadership from other functions (e.g. Product &amp; Engineering, BD and Community) to ensure that Marketing is aligned with the overall business strategy and goals</li> <li>Develop methods for data-driven decision making; set growth metrics for campaigns, engagement and events, and surface and communicate effectively about the analytical insights<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Requirements<br></strong><ul> <li>Bachelor's degree in business, marketing, communications or a related field</li> <li>(Optional but preferred) Masters degree in marketing or MBA</li> <li>8+ years of professional experience and 3+ years of people management experience</li> <li>3+ years of experience in a high-growth startup environment</li> <li>Experience in building and managing a high-performing marketing team</li> <li>In-depth knowledge of Layer-1 blockchain networks and DeFi, NFT and crypto gaming</li> <li>(Optional but preferred) Strong product marketing or developer marketing experience</li> <li>(Optional but preferred) 3+ years of full-time experience at a notable layer-1 blockchain network and/or DeFi/NFT/Gaming protocols</li> <li>Self-motivated to prioritize and manage workload and meet critical project deadlines</li> <li>Highly organized with strong attention to details</li> <li>Strong understanding of data/metrics that need to be tracked and investigated to understand success and performance in developer/user acquisition and engagement</li> <li>Excellent leadership, interpersonal and relationship management skills</li> <li>Superb spoken and written English<br><br> </li> </ul>This is a great time to join Oasis Foundation.<br><br><strong>Location: </strong>The role can be based anywhere with flexible and remote work options.<br><br><strong>Please note: This is a full-time role that will be paid in USDT OR USDC cryptocurrency</strong> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Oasis Network</company>
<location> NY New York US</location>
<tags>head-of-marketing, marketing, non-tech, executive, blockchain, crypto, defi, nft</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49640</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:10:26 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Sr Community Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ADN2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>We are ClubRare - The World's first community-centered Physical NFT marketplace for collectors. We connect the Real-world and the Metaverse. We are a community for people who trade the things we love.<br><br>We are a fully remote company with no fixed headquarters. As a distributed company, we embrace a diverse and inclusive culture that transcends geographical borders. Our team members come from all over the world and bring a rich array of experiences, perspectives, and life&gt;<br>We are deeply committed to fostering a culture of empathy, integrity, strategic thinking, innovation, leadership, and performance. These values drive everything we do, from the way we interact with our community and partners to the way we develop and deliver our products. It's our shared values that give us the strength and drive to become the open metaverse for collectors.<br><br><strong>What’s in It for You?<br></strong></p><ul> <li>Be a vital member of a cutting-edge project and take your career to the next level.</li> <li>Work from anywhere, on your own schedule, and be part of a team that shares your values and has a clear vision.</li> <li>Have the chance to shape the future of an innovative new model for cryptocurrency and blockchain applications.</li> <li>Get hands-on experience with the latest tech and systems, and challenge yourself to learn and grow.</li> <li>Play an active role in one of the most significant technological innovations in human history.</li> <li>Be compensated with a competitive salary paid in crypto for your dedication and efforts.</li> <li>Receive a competitive salary paid in crypto.<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Your Impact<br><br></strong>You will be managing our Discord and Twitter communities working with our Community Engagement lead and Marketing teams to define and distribute our social media strategy and content.<br><br>The ideal candidate will have a proven track record of delivering quantifiable brand growth, previous experience as a community manager/social media manager, and must also have an intimate knowledge of the crypto, NFT, and metaverse industry and keep up with current marketing trends in the Web3 space. This is not a regular community management role, as you will be responsible for building, managing, and nurturing a global and diverse community while growing and engaging global online communities across different channels to drive positive sentiment toward ClubRare and it's own ecosystem.<br><br><strong>Responsibilities<br></strong><ul> <li>Manage ClubRare’s Twitter, Discord, and Telegram communities and deliver high-quality content to promote NFT drops or any platform updates with the objective of building ClubRare's presence in the U.S. and globally. </li> <li>Design campaigns to drive user growth and engagement, and also educate users.</li> <li>Running contests, AMAs, virtual meet-ups, contests, and online shows in the community to introduce and promote both drops, guides, and educational content.</li> <li>Plan and develop high-quality engaging content, activities, and campaigns in our Discord and Twitter platofrms to boost community engagement.</li> <li>Shape the creation of Community Ambassador Programs and guidelines, Referral Programs, Bounty Campaigns, Virtual Events, games/trivia, and much more!</li> <li>Collect feedback from the community to identify and capture marketing opportunities, areas of improvement, and services.</li> <li>Assist with developing and enforcing best practices on Discord.</li> <li>Contributes to the ideation and drives the execution of engagement strategies and activation ideas to help improve the community experience.</li> <li>Monitoring member engagement, collecting feedback, and suggesting ways to improve.</li> <li>Comfortable with navigating through gray areas and ambiguity. </li> <li>Collaborate with the Marketing, Support, Product, and Dev team to deliver on company goals.<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Requirements<br></strong><ul> <li>Minimum 3+ years as a community manager or similar role. Knowledge and experience in community building.</li> <li>At least 1 year working on a Web3 project driving community engagement.</li> <li>Passionate about NFTs and Metaverse.</li> <li>English language fluency or mother tongue. Advanced English is a must.</li> <li>Deep experience with Twitter and Discord and have experience running events, town halls, virtual chats, and AMAs.</li> <li>Experience with Telegram and know how to leverage them strategically and tactically to meet objectives.</li> <li>Emotionally resilient and able to collaborate and communicate across a global team.</li> <li>Ability to introduce and moderate best practices or frameworks for community development and growth.</li> <li>Experience leading community initiatives such as AMAs, ambassador programs, advocacy programs, etc.</li> <li>Self-starter with experience using decentralized technologies, and previous experience in customer service and marketing.</li> <li>Able to work autonomously, set agenda, and prioritize work with minimal input.</li> <li>We are an all-remote company but prefer that you have availability during US work hours (PST←CT→EST) to facilitate better collaboration with your core team.<br><br> </li> </ul>At ClubRare, we believe that talent knows no boundaries. Our company is built on a foundation of collaboration and teamwork, and we believe that the best ideas can come from anywhere, that's why we encourage you to apply, no matter where you are located.<br><br>We are committed to creating a work environment that is inclusive and welcoming to all. As an equal-opportunity employer, we do not discriminate on the basis of race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, pregnancy, disability, age, veteran status, or any other characteristic. We believe that diversity is a source of strength and all qualified candidates will be given equal consideration for employment at ClubRare.<br><br>Discover more about ClubRare and what we stand for by visiting our website at www.clubrare.xyz When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>ClubRare</company>
<location> United States New York US</location>
<tags>community-manager, non-tech, blockchain, crypto, nft</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49639</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:06:14 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Junior Research Analyst</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kzM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Us:<br><br></strong>Blockworks is a fast-growing financial media brand that delivers news and insights about bitcoin and crypto to millions of investors.<br><br>Our editorial site, research, newsletters, podcasts and events provide investors with the critical analysis and information they need to make smarter decisions about digital assets.<br><br><strong>About The Role<br><br></strong>We are building a world-class research team at Blockworks, providing deep insights into various crypto assets through on-chain data with context, governance updates, and broader qualitative research. We cover topics before they become a mainstream narrative to provide alpha for our subscribers. Junior Analysts will work alongside Analysts and Senior analysts across our four teams: research, data and analytics, governance, and services.<br><br>Blockworks is looking for passionate, detail-oriented individuals to join our research team. As a crypto researcher, you will be responsible for creating in-depth reports and tracking on-chain metrics for various protocols, specifically DeFi-focused. There is also a lot of opportunity to grow your personal brand through Twitter, various podcast and Twitter Space appearances, and active participation in DAO governance.<br><br>This role is open for candidates who are working remote within North America as well as candidates who prefer to work from our New York office. Candidates who are able to work within 3 hours of ET is preferred. This role offers competitive compensation and significant opportunities for growth.<br><br><strong>The Role<br><br></strong>In this role, you will work directly with our Head of Research and will:<br></p><ul> <li>Conduct deep-dive research on topics like L1s, L2s, monolithic vs. modular stacks, incumbent and rising dApps, and much more. </li> <li>Communicate with our audience through telegram, discord, and other mediums about the state of the crypto industry and where it is moving. </li> <li>Work with data using SQL and Python to form analyses and explain them in charts and other data visualizations that are digestible. </li> <li>Wear many hats, contribute to many projects, and adapt to the needs of the team at a fast growing organization. </li> <li>Evaluate various tokenomic structures and their long-term sustainability and value capture. <br><br> </li> </ul><strong>What You’ll Bring<br></strong><ul> <li>Eager mentality to learn </li> <li>Passion for crypto, including a willingness to research new topics and change your opinions</li> <li>A strong understanding of various scaling architectures i.e. optimistic vs. zk rollups, app-specific chains, subnets, high throughput base layers, etc. </li> <li>Capable of working with data using SQL or Python, or the desire to learn is a plus </li> <li>Ability to swiftly comprehend complex topics and work independently in a fast-paced environment</li> <li>Ability to write long-form research about complex narratives and ideas in a way that is clear, cohesive, accurate, and can be understood by a general audience. </li> <li>A passion for DeFi and extensive experience using various dApps</li> <li>An understanding of smart contracts and how to use various block explorers</li> <li>Familiarity with all of the tools in the industry that are available to support you in the research process</li> <li>Experience being active within a DAO or regularly looking into various governance forums<br><br> </li> </ul><strong>Salary &amp; Benefits<br></strong><ul> <li>A commitment to an open, inclusive, and diverse work culture</li> <li>Competitive pay</li> <li>14 weeks of fully paid parental leave</li> <li>Fully paid medical, dental, and vision insurance for you + a significant portion covered for your dependents </li> <li>401(k) plan</li> <li>Remote work-station stipend</li> <li>Learning stipend</li> <li>Team happy hours and outings (even while remote!)</li> <li>Generous vacation and holiday policy</li> <li>Commuter benefits<br><br> </li> </ul>We know that diversity makes for the best problem-solving and creative thinking. We are dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team and encourage everyone to apply if your experience is close to what we are looking for.<br><br>Blockworks is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status.<br><br>Compensation Range: $70K - $80K<br><br> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Blockworks</company>
<location> United States US</location>
<tags>research, analyst, junior, entry-level, crypto, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49638</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:05:05 +0700</pubDate>
<title>General Interest</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gzM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Love Crypto but you don't currently see a position that is the right fit? Apply Here!</strong><br>We are always looking for motivated and passionate individuals to join the team at Foundry, a subsidiary of the blockchain industry’s most prolific and active investor, Digital Currency Group. If you have a passion for Crypto, but don't see a position that is a fit for you at this time, please submit your application here so we can consider you for future positions as we continue to grow.<br>At Foundry, we are working toward a common goal of empowering a decentralized infrastructure. Our team is passionate about the future of finance and is looking for other like-minded individuals who share in this vision. While we are inclusive and diverse in workforce and &gt;<br></p><strong>WHAT WE OFFER:</strong><br><ul> <li>The chance to work in a fast-paced and fun start-up environment with experienced industry leaders</li> <li>A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact</li> <li>Competitive base salary, bonus and incentive compensation Unlimited PTO / Flexible time off - work with your manager to take time off when you need it</li> <li>Professional development budget with flexibility for personal and professional growth</li> <li>Outstanding health insurance for employee, partner and dependents</li> <li>Life insurance, short-term &amp; long-term disability coverage</li> <li>401K plan with company contribution (Bermuda: Private pension plan with company contribution)</li> <li>Flexible spending programs for medical and dependent care (Not available for Bermuda positions)</li> <li>Paid parental leave</li> </ul><br><strong>ENVIRONMENT:</strong><br>Foundry takes pride in an environment which prioritizes our people. We insist that our people first culture builds the framework for all business operations.  <br>Employees have ample opportunities to voice thoughts, opinions, and ideas through weekly companywide meetings, monthly townhalls, and team outings and events.  <br>We emphasize the importance of each individual through engagement, teamwork, inclusion, and diversity efforts. <br>Foundry is an Equal Opportunity Employer and embraces diversity. We do not tolerate discrimination or harassment based on race, color, religion, marital status, gender (including pregnancy, childbirth or related medical conditions), gender identity, sexual orientation, parental status, national origin, age, disability, genetic information (including family medical history), political affiliation, military service, or any other non-merit-based factors protected under federal, state or local law. This policy applies to all terms and conditions of employment, including recruiting, hiring, placement, promotion, termination, layoff, transfer, leaves of absence, compensation, and training.<br><strong>ABOUT FOUNDRY:</strong><br>At Foundry, we are working toward a common goal of empowering a decentralized infrastructure. Our team is passionate about the future of finance and is looking for other like-minded individuals who share in this vision. While we are inclusive and diverse in workforce and &gt;<br>Foundry was created to meet the institutional demand for better capital access, efficiency, and transparency in the digital currency mining and staking industry.<br>As a Digital Currency Group company, Foundry taps unparalleled institutional expertise, capital, and market intelligence to provide North American bitcoin miners and global manufacturers with the resources to build, maintain, and secure decentralized networks.<br><strong>Disclaimer</strong><br>The above statements are intended to describe the general nature and level of work performed by employees assigned to this classification. They are not intended to be construed as an exhaustive list of all responsibilities, duties and skills required of personnel so classified. When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Foundry, a Digital Currency Group Company</company>
<location> NY Buffalo US</location>
<tags>blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49637</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:03:57 +0700</pubDate>
<title>General Interest - Studios Team</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=czM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Summary</strong><br>Are you passionate about building the Open Metaverse but don't see a job description here that fits your skillset? Submit your resume to this general interest position and we'll reach out if we find a good fit for you!<br><strong>About Mona</strong><br>Mona is a team of metaverse pioneers, empowering billions of people to create, collect, and share high quality 3D experiences on the blockchain. We exist to build innovative products, tools, and protocols that inspire and help creators tap into new income streams, accelerate the adoption of web3, and grow the open metaverse. With your help.</p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Mona</company>
<location> United States US</location>
<tags>blockchain</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49636</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 11:02:42 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Quantitative Trader</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=YzM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Injective Labs</strong><br>Injective Labs is trailblazing a new dawn for Web3 enabled finance. We are the core contributors to Injective, one of the fastest growing blockchains in the industry. Injective provides an interoperable smart contracts platform that is optimized for building decentralized finance applications. Interoperability is at the core of Injective, which is natively integrated with chains such as Ethereum, Cosmos and Solana. Developers can rapidly launch premier financial applications suited for mass adoption using Injective’s infrastructure and specialized DeFi primitives such as the world’s first fully on-chain order book.Our team has decades of experience spearheading the largest financial institutions and tech organizations. Injective is incubated by Binance and is backed by leading firms such as Jump Crypto, Pantera and Mark Cuban.<br>We are seeking a Quantitative Trader who will be responsible for the following job duties:<br>Trade cryptocurrency electronically for our own investment accounts by using highly specialized quantitative skills to buy and sell cryptocurrency in the decentralized financial trading platform;<br>Construct investment trading portfolio and develop trading strategies using quantitative skills.<br>Responsibilities:<br></p><ul> <li>Manage the trading accounts by constructing investment portfolio; </li> <li>Research and collect market information with a particular focus on cryptocurrency trading; </li> <li>Research and develop trading strategies for a particular focus on methodology selection, data collection and analysis, implementation and testing, prototyping, and performance evaluation, including algorithms development, simulation and backtesting; </li> <li>Develop tools and methods by using analytical and quantitative skills to analyze large financial datasets in cryptocurrency financial markets; </li> <li>Develop and create predictive modelling, clustering, time series analysis for purposes of data analysis; </li> <li>Contribute to back-end and front-end design, development, and testing for purposes of implementing models into the Injective trading platform. <br><br> </li> </ul>Requirements:<br><ul> <li>Master’s degree in mathematics, statistics, computer science, engineering, technology (including biotechnology), or related quantitative field</li> <li>Minimum of one year of related work experience in multi-exchange trading system<br> </li> </ul><br>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws. When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Injective Labs</company>
<location> United States New York US</location>
<tags>quantitative, quantitative-trader, trader, crypto, defi, ethereum, solana</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49634</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 08:42:09 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Quant Trader</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=QzM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p></p><p>At PINTU, we are building the #1 crypto platform in Indonesia and Southeast Asia. We know that 99% of new investors are underserved because many existing solutions cater to the 1% who are pros and early adopters; hence we provide an offering that helps even new investors learn, invest and interact with digital assets through our seamless &amp; user-friendly experience.</p><p>Pintu is looking for a Quant Trader/Researcher who will lead and execute proprietary market-making operations for our exchange. The position reports directly to CFO. The Quant Trader/Researcher will work closely with the engineering, risk management, and treasury ops team.</p><p><strong>Job Description :</strong></p><ul> <li>Develop proprietary market-making (”MM”) operations for Pintu Exchange:<ul> <li>Develop in-house quantitative trading &amp; risk management strategies/models for MM at Pintu Exchange that supports MM Goal Priorities.</li> <li>Collaborate with engineering, risk management, and treasury ops teams to orchestrate the implementation of semi/fully-automated quantitative trading strategies.</li> </ul> </li> <li>Build &amp; manage a team of MM quantitative researcher/trader(s), including task allocation &amp; mentorship.</li> <li>Quant strategies monitoring &amp; improvement :<ul> <li>Continuously monitor model parameters and back-test existing in-house MM strategies to meet the MM Goal Priorities</li> <li>Research &amp; identify new quantitative trading strategies that meets MM Goal Priorities</li> </ul> </li> </ul><p><strong>IMM Goal Priorities:</strong></p><ol> <li>Supports the improvement of Pintu Exchange liquidity;</li> <li>Satisfies internal risk parameters;</li> <li>improves MM’s risk-adjusted returns</li> </ol><p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p><ul> <li>5+ past professional quantitative research/trading experience in Global/ Regional MM Firms. Ideally has a minimum of 3 years in crypto and 2 years in trade-fi quant research/trading experience.</li> <li>Good understanding of market structures in both crypto (CEX &amp; DEX) and financial markets (e.g. FX).</li> <li>Past academic background in either in Comp-Sci, Statistics, Financial Engineering/Operation Research, or Mathematics.</li> <li>Extensive experience in programming languages such as Python/R/etc, or similar applicable programming languages.</li> <li>Excellent understanding of High Frequency Trading (”HFT”) strategies (a must) and/or Algo-Trading (plus).</li> <li>Excellent communication, leadership, &amp; interpersonal skills.</li> <li>Had experience in managing a team.</li> <li>CFA &amp; FRM is a plus.</li> <li>Timezone: Max 3 time zones away from JKT/SG (or willing to relocate to Singapore/Bali/Jakarta).</li> </ul><ol></ol> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Pintu</company>
<location> Setiabudi ID</location>
<tags>trader, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49630</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 08:40:48 +0700</pubDate>
<title>HR Generalist</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=AzM2kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<section id="job-openings" class="job-openings"> <div class="container"> <div class="content-intro"><p><em>Founded in 2018 and already valued at over $8 billion, Fireblocks is a SaaS platform that helps companies to create innovative products on the blockchain and manage day-to-day crypto operations. Fireblocks is trusted by some of the largest financial institutions, banks, globally-recognized brands, and Web3 companies in the world, including BNY Mellon, BNP Paribas, ANZ Bank, Revolut, and thousands more, to securely scale digital asset operations through the Fireblocks Network and MPC-based wallet infrastructure. We have offices in New York, London, Tel Aviv, and Singapore, and we are continuing to expand our teams to reach new customers globally.</em></p></div> <p><span>APAC HR Generalist</span></p> <p>Founded in 2018 by cybersecurity veterans Michael Shaulov, Idan Ofrat, and Pavel Berengoltz, Fireblocks is an easy-to-use platform to create innovative products on the blockchain and manage day-to-day crypto operations.</p> <p>Fireblocks is trusted by some of the largest financial institutions, banks, globally-recognized brands, and Web3 companies in the world, including BNY Mellon, BNP Paribas, ANZ Bank, Moonpay, Animoca Brands, Revolut, eToro, Crypto.com, and more, to securely scale digital asset operations through the Fireblocks Network and MPC-based wallet infrastructure. Valued at over US$8 billion, Fireblocks serves thousands of organizations, has secured the transfer of over $4 trillion in digital assets, and has a unique insurance policy that covers assets in storage &amp; transit.</p> <p><span>About The Role</span></p> <p><span>As the HR Generalist, you will play a key role in driving organizational culture and values, continuously assessing the organizational needs, devising solutions, and coaching managers. You will focus on recruiting, onboarding, engaging, growing, and developing our people, as well as adapting cross-organizational HR processes and leading initiatives to best support the team’s development and growth.</span></p> <p><span>This position will build the foundation of our People and Talent Acquisition processes across APAC and represents an excellent opportunity to impact the future growth of the company from day 1. </span></p> <p> </p> <p><span>Key Responsibilities</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Responsibility for the full employee life cycle, recruiting and onboarding to off-boarding. </span></li> <li><span>Act as a full-cycle recruiter for open positions running sourcing campaigns, executing interviews, and closing candidates.</span></li> <li><span>Support and execute people and culture  strategy in APAC, while closely collaborating with the global team.</span></li> <li><span>Provide strategic business partnership, thought partnership, and coaching to employees and mid-level managers </span></li> <li><span>Proactively assess the organizational needs and root causes, suggest recommendations, guide informed decision-making, and implement appropriate solutions</span></li> <li><span>Work closely with the MOM (Ministry Of Manpower) on ongoing employee matters such as Job Postings, EP applications, MOM surveys, etc</span></li> <li><span>Partner with the local service providers to support matters such as Payroll, EOR employees, etc.</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Requirements</span></p> <ul> <li><span>3+ years as an People Business Partner or HR Generalist at a Tech company - a must</span></li> <li><span>2+ years experience in recruiting both technical and non-technical positions</span></li> <li><span>Experience in a global environment/scaling teams</span></li> <li><span>A proven track record of successfully positioning as a trusted partner and impacting teams and leaders</span></li> <li><span>Motivated by a dynamic and changing environment</span></li> <li><span>Collaborator and a team player - an inclusive mindset and ability to build great relationships at all levels of the organization</span></li> <li><span>Strong verbal and written communication and influencing skills </span></li> <li><span>Analytical, critical thinking, and problem-solving skills, experience in using data to identify insights and trends that drive action, and exercises solid judgment.</span></li> </ul> <p><span><em>Fireblocks will be prioritizing candidates who do not need visa sponsorships due to the immediate need and nature of the role</em></span></p> <div class="content-conclusion"> <p><em>Fireblocks' mission is to enable every business to easily and securely access digital assets and cryptocurrencies. In order to do that, we strongly believe our workforce should be as diverse as our clients, and this is why we embrace diversity and inclusion in all its forms. </em></p> <h6><em>Please see our candidate privacy policy here.</em></h6> </div> <div id="grnhse_app"></div> </div> </section> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Fireblocks</company>
<location>Location: Singapore</location>
<tags>hr, non-tech, blockchain, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49537</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 03:11:05 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Senior Marketing Manager (Las Vegas Office)</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=czM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p>VIMworld Inc is seeking a Senior Marketing Manager to lead our marketing efforts in Las Vegas, NV. As the Senior Marketing Manager, you will be responsible for driving customer acquisition, managing external projects, and overseeing paid social media channels. The ideal candidate will have strong experience in digital marketing, community marketing, and social media channels. We are looking for a creative thinker who can work collaboratively with partners and internal teams to develop and execute innovative marketing campaigns that drive business results. The candidate must be a data-driven, out-of-the-box thinker, an extrovert with a startup mentality, and 4 -6 years of experience in a marketing management role. Multilingual is a plus.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Take ownership of customer acquisition and external projects expansion</li> <li>Manage and execute paid social media campaigns</li> <li>Lead the development and execution of marketing campaigns across various channels, including email, social media, and content marketing</li> <li>Work collaboratively with internal teams, including product development, design, and content to develop marketing strategies and materials</li> <li>Analyze and report on the performance of marketing campaigns, using KPIs to measure success</li> <li>Develop and maintain relationships with partners and external vendors</li> <li>Brainstorm creative ideas and contribute to a culture of innovation and out-of-the-box thinking</li> <li>Develop and implement marketing communications materials - videos, newsletters, social media content, news articles and participate in podcast, online spaces</li> <li>Stay up to date with shifting trends in our industry, client demographics and expectations, and key stakeholders’ requirements</li> </ul> <p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p> <ul> <li>Bachelor’s degree in Sales, Digital Marketing, Business Administration, or a related field</li> <li>At least 4 - 6 years of experience in digital marketing or social media marketing role</li> <li>Strong experience in digital marketing, community marketing, user acquisition and social media content</li> <li>Experience in managing paid social media channels</li> <li>Experience in working with a startup or fast-paced environment</li> <li>Multilingual skills are a plus</li> <li>Strong communication, collaboration, and project management skills</li> <li>Ability to work in a data-driven environment</li> <li>Experience in the blockchain, Defi, and NFT platforms is a plus</li> </ul> <p>VIMworld Inc. offers a competitive salary, a comprehensive benefits package. We value integrity, collaboration, and hard work, and are committed to providing our employees with the resources and support they need to succeed.</p> <p>If you are a creative, data-driven, and collaborative marketer with a passion for blockchain, Defi, and smart NFT platforms, we encourage you to apply for this exciting opportunity. As a Senior Marketing Manager at VIMworld Inc, you will have the opportunity to work with a dynamic and innovative team at the forefront of our industry and contribute to our growth and success. To apply please submit your resume and cover letter, for consideration. We look forward to hearing from you!</p> <p></p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>VIMworld</company>
<location> NV Las Vegas US</location>
<tags>marketing-manager, office, marketing, non-tech, senior, blockchain, defi, nft</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49530</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 May 2023 00:40:54 +0700</pubDate>
<title>HelpDesk Agent</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=AzM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="careersSingleRole_mainText__Rmdo- rawHTMLRoot rawHTML_rich__2VTkc"> <p><span>Our mission is to unlock the collaborative power of communities by making Web3 universally easy to use, access, and build on</span></p> <p><span>Working with ConsenSys puts you at the </span><strong>forefront of an evolving paradigm</strong><span>, transforming our society for the better. We fundamentally believe blockchain is the next generation of technology that can lay the foundation for a more just and equitable society. </span></p> <p><span>Blockchain tech is just over 10 years old. Ethereum itself is still a toddler and we’re far from reaching our full potential. You’ll get to work on the tools, infrastructure, and apps that scale these platforms to billions of users. </span></p> <p><span>You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas, and frameworks from your peers, and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the </span><strong>top of your game</strong><span>. You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the </span><strong>edge of our ecosystem</strong><span>. ConsenSys alumni have moved on to become tech entrepreneurs, CEOs, and team leads at tech companies.</span><span> </span></p> <p> </p> <p><span><strong>About Customer Success</strong><span><br></span></span></p> <p><span><span>The Customer Success team in ConsenSys is focused on exactly that: making our customers successful. The team is designed to complement ConsenSys products by creating a holistic well-rounded experience for our customers and users.</span></span></p> <p><span>We focus on 3 areas:</span></p> <p><span><strong>Customer experience</strong> - Ensuring that our customers and users are engaged, and satisfied with ConsenSys products and services.</span><br><span><strong>Brand protection</strong> - Maintaining and elevating the ConsenSys brand and overall reputation through our customers and users, and their feedback</span><br><span><strong>Continuous improvement</strong> - Learning and adapting to the customers' needs and providing feedback to the products allows ConsenSys to maximize its market potential and be a better fit for a wider audience</span></p> <p> </p> <p><strong>What you’ll do</strong><span><br></span></p> <p><span>The Help Desk team acts as a first point of contact for customers, their task is to triage the support tickets, solve the most common problems users may have and gather all the necessary information before escalating to the higher support levels.</span></p> <p><span>We are seeking a detail-oriented, thorough and organized candidate to join our growing team. You’ll need excellent problem-solving, communication and interpersonal skills, along with patience, a customer-friendly attitude and the ability to work in a team.</span></p> <h4><strong>Responsibilities will include</strong></h4> <ul> <li><span>Respond to customer support requests by following the agreed procedures.</span></li> <li><span>Research questions using available information resources and advise user on appropriate action</span></li> <li><span>As part of a global support team, working on establishing operational protocols and standards</span></li> <li><span>Work in shifts in order to cover an extended time frame including evenings and weekends</span></li> </ul> <p><strong>Would be great if you brought this to the role</strong></p> <p><span>Minimum Requirements </span></p> <ul> <li><span>Excellent communication skills (writing and speaking) in English </span></li> <li><span>Understanding of Ethereum and the blockchain ecosystem </span></li> <li><span>Enthusiasm for continual learning and interest in blockchain technologies </span></li> </ul> <p><span>Preferred Qualifications </span></p> <ul> <li><span>Student, Bachelor's degree from a technical university </span></li> <li><span>Prior experience in a service desk/Help desk role</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Nice to have </span></p> <ul> <li><span>Knowledge of a programming language</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Don't meet all the requirements? Don't sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you've got what it takes for our chaotic-but-fun, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway, detailing your relevant transferable skills in your cover letter. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we're ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role</span><span>.</span></p> <p><span><em data-stringify-type="italic">The salary range for US-based candidates only will be determined throughout the interview process depending on experience and skills. Candidates should anticipate a base salary (not including bonus, equity or other benefits) of $USD 50,000 - $123,000</em></span></p> <p><em><span>ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law. ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found (https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/)</span></em><em><span>.</span></em></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Consensys</company>
<location>CANADA - Remote, LATAM - Remote, UNITED STATES - Remote</location>
<tags>remote, blockchain, ethereum</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49529</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 23:14:26 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Blockchain Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kjM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Blockchain Engineer</strong>⚡</p><p><strong>New York </strong></p><p><strong> </strong></p><p>Storm2 is currently partnering with a digital-first art network that is changing the landscape of art collection through the power of blockchain technology. Their cutting-edge artwork transaction database allows art collectors, investors, and managers to tokenize physical artworks and incorporate them into traditional financial instruments.</p><br><p>They are looking for a Blockchain Engineer to join their growing team and directly build out the future of art collection by working on their flagship product. This is a unique opportunity to work for a one-of-a-kind company in the space.</p><br><p><strong><u>Responsibilities</u></strong></p><br><ul> <li>Create cutting-edge blockchain apps and decentralized applications (DApps), such as smart contracts, non-fungible tokens (NFTs), and digital certificates.</li> <li>Work with several blockchain platforms and infrastructures, such as Algorand and its SDKs, Polygon, and Avalanche.</li> <li>Oversee and develop all phases of contract development, including requirement collecting, design, development, testing, deployment, and event monitoring.</li> </ul><br><br><p><strong><u>Requirements</u></strong></p><br><ul> <li>4-5 years of professional blockchain engineer experience.</li> <li>Knowledge in creating successful smart contracts using <strong>Solidity</strong>.</li> <li>Practical knowledge of one or more blockchain technologies in a production setting, ideally <strong>Algorand, Ethereum</strong>, and/or <strong>Polygon</strong>.</li> <li>Proficiency in <strong>Python</strong> and/or <strong>Typescript</strong>.</li> <li>Experience with <strong>web3.js</strong>, <strong>ethers.js</strong>, or similar libraries.</li> </ul><br><p><strong><u>Bonus</u></strong></p><ul> <li>Familiarity with REACH</li> <li>Experience with Serverless architecture, AWS Lambda, Azure Functions or similar</li> <li>Experience with financial products or fintech</li> </ul><br><p>Why Apply?</p><ul> <li>Hybrid work schedule opportunities.</li> <li>Social gaming evenings with activities and art exhibitions.</li> <li>Competitive salary and vacation days.</li> </ul><br><br><p><em>🌎New York</em></p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Storm2</company>
<location> United States New York US</location>
<tags>dev, blockchain, aws, ethereum, solidity, typescript</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49528</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 23:12:00 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Founding Blockchain Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gjM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <div>We are building DeFi for the future of custody<br><br> </div> <div>We expect all DAOs, institutions and retail users to custody their crypto with a permissionless programmable MPC layer. Why?<br><br> </div> <div>As it is trustless, user don’t have to worry about counterparty risk. It is the key to unlock great UX supporting all chains and enabling to set up transaction rules (e.g. 2FA, spending limits). Finally, due to its permissionlessness, similarly to Ethereum it enables rapid innovation leading to better custody products than stand-alone MPC solutions.<br><br> </div> <div>Building on top of such an emerging solution, our aim is to build the DeFi infrastructure enabling a Coinbase like trading experience for applications building on top of us. This includes building a liquidity management layer which can be compared to how Coinbase deposit addresses and their database work together. This makes assets across all chains tradeable on the MPC blockchain without settlement on the underlying chains. Additionally, we want to build applications leveraging this layer such as cross-chain swapping and lending.<br><br> </div> <div>Our team (Justin &amp; Alex) started building products at an early age and in crypto specifically won $30k at ETH global hackathons. We have a strong academic background (Cambridge), industry experience from high growth startups, big-tech (Amazon) and one of Europe’s most renowned VC firms. We are backed by node.capital (who built Colored Coins together with Vitalik), and other awesome VCs/builders in the space, with backgrounds at Delphi Digital, ETH Global, Kava, Parity.<br><br> </div> <div>About the position<br><br> </div> <div>We are looking for a Founding Blockchain Engineer to join our team <strong>in Lisbon (in person strongly preferred)</strong> from <strong>June/July 2023.</strong> We aim to build a very small but massively impactful team. We compensate above average and as a founding team member you will get a substantial token allocation.<br><br> </div> <div>In this position, you will have the following responsibilities:<br><br> </div> <ul> <li> <strong>Smart Contracts:</strong> Building on-chain programs and writing tests using Rust, with a focus on security, performance, maintainability and composability.</li> <li> <strong>Protocol Architecture:</strong> Designing and building key technical components for the protocol</li> <li> <strong>Mentorship:</strong> Supporting junior engineers in the team</li> <li> <strong>Product discovery:</strong> Ensuring that we are building the right things for our users</li> </ul> <div>Requirements<br><br> </div> <ul> <li>Most importantly: fit of values (see below)</li> <li>Solid experience in core blockchain protocol design</li> <li>Confidence in writing secure and high quality code in Rust strongly preferred</li> <li>DeFi protocol design experience is a plus</li> <li>Experience with Typescript, Move / Sui’s concept of objects is a plus</li> </ul> <div>Values<br><br> </div> <div>At X2, we think you will thrive if you can identify with the following values:<br><br> </div> <ul> <li> <strong>We are entrepreneurial.</strong> We have a strong sense of initiative and ownership. We can operate independently under uncertainty, and prioritise work effectively. We act with conviction; have strong opinions, but loosely held and don’t need to get approval if we want to make an informed bet.</li> <li> <strong>We strive for excellence.</strong> We have the intensity and motivation to perform at a world class level. Even in tough situations, we remain optimistic and our inner drive keeps us going. We hold each other accountable to the highest standards regarding security, code quality and UX.</li> <li> <strong>We are</strong> <strong>highly curious and learn quickly.</strong> We are building on a new primitive in crypto. Hence, we value speed of learning more than experience in the space. Also, we have to rethink existing primitives and the curiosity to explore the solution space is key to our success.</li> <li> <strong>We are collaborative.</strong> We value ****truthful and transparent communication and have a radically candid feedback culture. We champion diversity because it is essential to our ability to think differently.</li> </ul> <div><br></div> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>X2</company>
<location>Lisbon</location>
<tags>founding-member, dev, blockchain, blockchain-engineer, crypto, defi, ethereum, node, rust, solidity, typescript</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49525</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 22:19:47 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Growth Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=UjM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>**About Us**<br><br>Colony is an open-source framework for Decentralised Autonomous Organisations (DAOs). Our tools enable distributed teams to distribute authority and collectively manage the organisation’s money and make decisions. As one of the leading projects in a rapidly growing space, we offer an opportunity to get in at the ground floor of what many predict to be the next major social technology. <br><br>Colony is a fully distributed team that occasionally convenes somewhere in the world to work and hang out together. The rest of the time, we communicate over Discord. It’s a dynamic environment that requires grit, flexibility, self-motivation, and a sense of emoji etiquette.<br><br>**The Role**<br><br>Colony is gearing up for the launch of a major new version of its application. Your job will be to get it into the hands of users.<br><br>You will be responsible for crafting and executing Colony's comprehensive go-to-market strategy. Your efforts will focus on enhancing brand visibility and accelerating product adoption among target customers.<br><br>**Areas of ownership**<br><br>**Strategic:** Design and implement the go to market strategy for “New Colony”.<br>**Operational:** Assemble, lead, and manage a high-performing growth team<br>**Tactical:** Actively execute hands-on tasks and initiatives.<br>**Financial:** Define and manage growth budgets prioritising ROI<br><br>**Key Responsibilities:**<br><br>- Design and execute strategic growth plans aligned with overall business Objectives and Key Results (OKRs) to boost brand awareness and customer acquisition.<br>- Analyze market trends, competitor strategies, and leverage data-driven decisions to drive growth.<br>- Build, lead, and manage a high-performing growth team to achieve company objectives.<br>- Develop, implement, and evaluate growth campaigns using key performance indicators (KPIs) and optimize budgets for maximum ROI.<br>- Collaborate with cross-functional teams and maintain strong relationships with industry partners, influencers, and media outlets.<br>- Stay informed on the latest marketing trends, tools, best practices, and developments in DAOs and blockchain technology.<br><br>**About You**<br><br>The ideal candidate will possess a strong drive for self-motivation and have a proven track record of successfully bringing a B2C SaaS product to market, capturing market share, and excelling within industry sectors. You should be prepared to discuss your achievements, the obstacles you encountered in terms of product adoption, and the strategies you employed to overcome these challenges.<br><br>We are seeking a candidate who excels at both strategizing and hands-on execution, as well as delegating tasks to specialists. While building a team is essential, it takes time, so we require someone capable of executing their strategies independently. If you're not prepared to actively contribute in both planning and implementation, kindly refrain from applying.<br><br>**Minimum Qualifications:**<br><br>- 8+ years of experience in growth marketing, with a focus on B2C SaaS startups.<br>- 2+ years of experience working within a distributed team.<br>- Proven track record of taking startups to market and achieving traction.<br>- Demonstrable success in winning market share and dominating sectors, backed by clear numbers and evidence.<br><br>**Minimum Competencies:**<br><br>- Highly organised and detail-oriented.<br>- Proven ability to create and execute structured marketing plans and campaigns.<br>- Excellent leadership and team management skills.<br>- Exceptional analytical, strategic thinking, and problem-solving abilities.<br>- Strong communication and interpersonal skills.<br>- Diligent and committed to excellence.<br>- Strong time management skills, with the ability to prioritise tasks effectively and manage multiple projects simultaneously.<br>- Results-driven and goal-oriented, consistently striving to meet or exceed objectives and performance targets.<br>- Skilled in developing and implementing efficient processes and workflows.<br>- Adaptable and resilient, able to navigate challenges and adjust plans as needed to achieve desired outcomes.<br>- Embraces a collaborative approach, fostering a positive team environment and effectively communicating with team members, stakeholders, and external partners.<br><br>**Bonus Points:**<br><br>- Expertise in developing growth strategies for DAOs and blockchain technology projects.<br>- Familiarity with growth tools and tactics specific to the blockchain industry.<br>- Experience in managing growth campaigns for decentralised autonomous organisations (DAOs) or similar projects.<br><br>### **What we offer**<br><br>- 100% remote work environment with no geographic limitations<br>- 100% transparency in all communication and decision-making processes<br>- Idea meritocracy, where the best ideas are embraced regardless of the source<br>- Friendly, non-hierarchical culture with a focus on meaningful work and no “office” politics<br>- Laptop policy with 50% contribution towards purchasing your own device<br>- Flexibility in working hours, with emphasis on delivering quality work output<br>- Unlimited time-off policy, based on mutual agreement with team members and individual responsibility<br>- UBB (Universal Basic Budget) of £1200 to be utilized towards anything beneficial to the project, such as personal development, team co-working, attending conferences, etc.<br>- Token allocation<br><br>Please apply by sending your CV and a cover letter to growthlead@colony.io.</p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Colony</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>growth, lead, blockchain, brand-marketing, business-development, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49520</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 17:55:49 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Namada and Anoma Community Development Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=AjM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <h2>About Heliax</h2> <p>Heliax is a remote-first public goods lab which researches, develops, deploys, and maintains open-source protocols &amp; mechanisms designed to serve the everyday needs of humanity. Using this, we build vertically integrated open-source products and networks that form coherent open systems which are capable of acting as an alternative to existing exploitative paradigms.</p> <p>Heliax’s work includes the Anoma protocol, a novel architecture that is intent-centric, privacy-preserving protocol for decentralised counterparty discovery, solving, &amp; multi-chain atomic settlement; Namada, a proof-of-stake L1 for interchain asset-agnostic privacy, designed to bring the best privacy to the multichain; Juvix and Vamp-IR, in the domain of languages for dApps and ZK circuits.</p> <h2> <br>Role Overview</h2> <p>We are looking for a community development lead to join Heliax as soon as possible. You’ll be working directly with the co-founders and frequently collaborate with the rest of the team members across all functions, including product, research and engineering teams.​</p> <p>You will support and contribute to community building, from setting up, improving, and engaging with the communities on Discord, Reddit, Twitter, and so on – and everything in between. You will also manage, execute, and oversee community programs, narratives, and campaigns to grow and steward the Anoma and Namada communities, as well as model the story of public goods including Namada and Anoma and the broader vision to the world.</p> <p>​The ideal candidate is someone who is native to the Internet, sometimes you spend more time interacting with virtual communities than real-world people. You’ve built and grown digital communities before and love doing it. You're a hyper-motivated, creative, flexible, and detail-oriented community builder, with clear focus on solving problems, bringing ideas to the table, and building long-term relationships – who is maximally aligned with the vision and values of Anoma, Namada, and Heliax.​</p> <h2> <br>What you'll do</h2> <ul> <li>Create and execute key community campaigns aiming to reach various target potential community members to grow the community, model Anoma/Namada’s vision and values, help coordinate the decentralised ecosystem and foster synergistic collaborations among everyone.</li> <li>Be part of the community and engage with it on a daily basis.</li> <li>Craft compelling and differentiated community materials, which include articles, social media posts (Twitter, Reddit, newsletters, etc), smaller activities and programs</li> <li>Ensure that all the research, products, innovations, and ecosystem-wide updates are known to the communities and encourage them to spread the word</li> <li>Craft FAQs and reference materials about the products and co-founder’s POV to help other community members, ecosystem partners, and individuals who want to help</li> <li>Research, identify, and track new opportunities to elevate Anoma &amp; Namada and the co-founders community game</li> <li>Manage all aspects of community platforms and partner relations, including building and maintaining long term relationships</li> <li>Help lead crisis response. You’ll also help refine our strategic response process</li> <li>Monitor community platforms, be the key point of contact for support and respond appropriately to inquiries and issues as they arise</li> <li>Represent Anoma, Namada, Heliax as a spokesperson as needed</li> </ul> <h2> <br>Your background</h2> <ul> <li>Obviously, you're excellent at verbal and written communication skills and love the virtual communities and the internet. Make sure to share your past work, including blog posts, tweets, Discord setups, forums you moderate, etc.</li> <li>You’re super, super organised and have a lot of attention to detail. You’re a creative, strategic, self-starter who can synthesise complex information, problem solving, and project management – basically you can make big contributions without requiring constant management and guidance</li> <li>A good baseline in understanding of protocols, technology and crypto – otherwise you’re able to get yourself up-to-speed very quickly with the latest, no matter how technical the topics are</li> <li>A knowledge of and interest in video creation and editing, as well as any other formats of content</li> <li>Telling stories feels natural to you: you’re inspired by what you read about and observe, have intuition about what will “work,” and can synthesise multiple inputs to bring strong storylines to life with minimal oversight</li> <li>You love working with other hoomans, deeply collaborative, and look for opportunities to have a greater impact through cross-functional, integrated marketing</li> <li>You have past experience navigating complex issues / crises, and the ability to see around corners and anticipate questions</li> <li>You’re personally aligned with the vision and values of Anoma and Namada</li> </ul> <h2> <br>Misc</h2> <p>Remote, but you can join the team at our current offices in Zug, London, or Berlin. When remote, preferred if mostly located within (+/- 3 hours) Central European time zones.</p> <p>Ideally someone who enjoys travel, nature and hiking. Often we find that protocols are best designed not in a meeting room but rather on a trail 🏔️.</p> <p><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Heliax</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>community-manager, non-tech, lead, remote, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49519</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 17:49:16 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Namada and Anoma Communications Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kTM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <h2>About Heliax</h2> <p>Heliax is a remote-first public goods lab which researches, develops, deploys, and maintains open-source protocols &amp; mechanisms designed to serve the everyday needs of humanity. Using this, we build vertically integrated open-source products and networks that form coherent open systems which are capable of acting as an alternative to existing exploitative paradigms.</p> <p>Heliax’s work includes the Anoma protocol, a novel architecture that is intent-centric, privacy-preserving protocol for decentralised counterparty discovery, solving, &amp; multi-chain atomic settlement; Namada, a proof-of-stake L1 for interchain asset-agnostic privacy, designed to bring the best privacy to the multichain; Juvix and Vamp-IR, in the domain of languages for dApps and ZK circuits.</p> <h2> <br>Role Overview</h2> <p>We are looking for a communications lead to join Heliax as soon as possible. You’ll be working directly with the co-founders and frequently collaborate with the rest of the team members across all functions, including product, research and engineering teams.</p> <p>You will support and contribute to content, from press work to marketing plans to social media and everything in between. You will also manage and oversee programs, narratives, and campaigns to tell the story of public goods including Namada and Anoma and the broader vision to the world.</p> <p>The ideal candidate will be a hyper-motivated, creative, flexible, and detail-oriented storyteller, with clear focus on solving problems, bringing ideas to the table, and building relationships – who is maximally aligned with the vision and values of Anoma, Namada, and Heliax.</p> <h2> <br>What you'll do</h2> <ul> <li>Create and execute key communication campaigns aiming to reach various target audiences, maximise brand awareness, further the reputation</li> <li>Craft compelling and differentiated communication materials, which include articles, social media posts (Twitter, Reddit, newsletters, etc)</li> <li>Ensure that all the research, products, innovations, and ecosystem-wide updates are known to the world</li> <li>Craft PR materials – position pieces, reactive statements, media pitches, etc. – to tell the story of the products and elevate co-founder’s POV</li> <li>Research, identify, and track new opportunities to elevate Anoma &amp; Namada’s story and co-founders</li> <li>Develop, prep and execute thought leadership campaigns for Anoma &amp; Namada co-founders, counselling them to more effectively tell stories, manage crises, and model Anoma’s vision and values through storytelling</li> <li>Manage all aspects of media and partner relations, including building and maintaining relationships with media of all kinds</li> <li>Help lead crisis response. You’ll also help refine our strategic response process</li> <li>Monitor media, social media, and community platforms, be the key point of contact for support and respond appropriately to inquiries and issues as they arise</li> <li>Represent Anoma, Namada, Heliax as a spokesperson as needed</li> </ul> <h2> <br>Your background</h2> <ul> <li>Obviously, you're excellent at verbal and written communication skills and love doing it. Make sure to share your past work, including blog posts, tweets, posts in forums, etc.</li> <li>You’re super, super organised and have a lot of attention to detail. You’re a creative, strategic, self-starter who can synthesise complex information, problem solving, and project management – basically you can make big contributions without requiring constant management and guidance</li> <li>A good baseline in understanding of protocols, technology and crypto – otherwise you’re able to get yourself up-to-speed very quickly with the latest, no matter how technical the topics are</li> <li>A knowledge of and interest in video creation and editing, as well as any other formats of content</li> <li>Telling stories feels natural to you: you’re inspired by what you read about and observe, have intuition about what will “work,” and can synthesise multiple inputs to bring strong storylines to life with minimal oversight</li> <li>You love working with other hoomans, deeply collaborative, and look for opportunities to have a greater impact through cross-functional, integrated marketing</li> <li>You have past experience navigating complex issues / crises, and the ability to see around corners and anticipate questions</li> <li>You’re personally aligned with the vision and values of Anoma and Namada</li> </ul> <h2> <br>Misc</h2> <p>Remote, but you can join the team at our current offices in Zug, London, or Berlin. When remote, preferred if mostly located within (+/- 3 hours) Central European time zones.</p> <p>Ideally someone who enjoys travel, nature and hiking. Often we find that protocols are best designed not in a meeting room but rather on a trail 🏔️.</p> <p><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Heliax</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>pr, non-tech, lead, marketing-communication, remote, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49513</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 16:24:02 +0700</pubDate>
<title>API3 Sentinel </title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MTM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <div> <strong> (Remote)</strong> API3 is seeking Sentinels to join our remote team and contribute to the development of our web3 products. As an API3 Sentinel, you will work closely with our development team and be responsible for monitoring our system APIs, partner APIs, errors, chats, and other critical areas. <br><br>Your role will be vital in maintaining the stability and performance of our products. <br><br><strong>Responsibilities:</strong> <br>• Monitor system APIs, errors, chats, charts, and other critical areas <br>• Spot abnormalities and escalate issues as necessary<br> <br><strong>Requirements:</strong> <br>• Ability to spot abnormalities and identify potential issues <br>• Good problem-solving skills and attention to detail <br>• Ability to work independently and in a remote team environment • Willingness to learn and adapt to new monitoring tools and technologies <br>• Flexibility to sometimes work on public holidays A basic understanding of EVM blockchains is a plus. <br><br>We offer fully remote work, and the opportunity to work on cutting-edge web3 products with a talented team of developers. If you have a passion for blockchain technology and want to contribute to shaping the future of the industry, please apply with your resume at jobs@api3.org <br><br> </div> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>API3 DAO</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>api, ai, blockchain, customer-support, dao, evm, quality-assurance, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49512</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 15:45:03 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Growth Marketing Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=ITM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p>Boson enables the decentralized exchange of physical assets- tokenised as redeemable NFTs.</p> <p>Boson Protocol solves the problem of fair exchange within e-commerce, without the need for trusted intermediaries or counterparties.  Instead, Buyer and Seller make commitments to trade within smart contracts encoded with game theory, and tokenized as redeemable NFTs.</p> <p>Buyers have assurance, that either they can redeem the NFT for the physical item or their get their money back. </p> <p>Sellers can Tokenize, transfer and trade any physical Thing as a redeemable NFT.</p> <p>Developers can easily build dCommerce dapps and integrations.</p> <p>No need to trust Sellers or intermediaries, simply input your payment and receive the item or your money back.</p> <p>Boson Protocol mediates commerce transactions of real-world assets using smart contracts — without a centralized intermediary. Tokenize, transfer and trade any physical Thing as an NFT.https://www.bosonprotocol.io/</p> <h2>Job Description</h2> <p><strong>What you will do</strong></p> <p>We are looking for a talented Growth Marketer to take the lead with growth strategies on behalf of our brands. Reporting into the senior team, your duties will include identifying and running high-potential growth experiments, tracking and improving conversion rates, and working with product and engineering teams around wider growth initiatives. Ultimately your job is to find channels that deliver users, products that delight them, and strategies that increase revenue. Growth can mean a lot of things. If you’re the kind of marketer that is able to combine creative nous with analytical rigour, we’d love to meet you.</p> <p><strong>Key Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Work with cross-functional teams (Product, Services, Sales) to establish growth strategies that support our clients’ revenue goals.</li> <li>Create, manage and optimise user acquisition campaigns across a range of new and established channels.</li> <li>Conceive and execute on a wide range of content-driven campaigns, working with designers, copywriters and videographers.</li> <li>Improve websites and landing pages in a creative, rigorous and data driven manner.</li> <li>Create better customer journeys using both qualitative and quantitative data to inform decision making.</li> <li>Develop better CRM and lead nurturing processes.</li> <li>Advise on SEO and targeted backlink campaigns.</li> <li>Provide high quality reporting around campaign, website and product performance, on a regular and ad hoc basis.</li> <li>Prepare and present recommendations, reports, and findings from experiments, all the way up to the executive level.</li> </ul> <p><strong>Minimum Requirements</strong></p> <ul> <li>3+ years’ experience in growth marketing and/or product management, with a strong track record of success, backed by results and samples of past projects/ campaigns</li> <li>Full stack marketer: Demonstrable experience using a wide range of digital marketing platforms, covering areas like SEO, paid search, paid social and conversion tracking</li> <li>Advanced knowledge of leading digital ad platforms (including Facebook, Google, Twitter &amp; LinkedIn) and experience in platform-specific content creation</li> <li>Strong working knowledge of statistics, and modern analytics platforms</li> <li>Solid project management skills: ability to lead and collaborate with cross-functional partners, prioritise high impact activities, and keep complex projects moving forward</li> <li>Outstanding written and oral communication skills</li> <li>Competent working in a fast-paced environment with multiple stakeholders</li> <li>Basic technical knowledge of popular programing languages (ie. HTML, React), agile methodology, and experience working with engineering teams</li> </ul> <p><strong>Benefits of working with us</strong></p> <ul> <li>Competitive salary</li> <li>Fully remote work - work from anywhere in the world</li> <li>Flexible working hours with a high degree of autonomy </li> <li>6% matching pension contribution scheme (UK) or equivalent in other countries</li> <li>25 days holiday plus 8 days bank holidays (UK) or equivalent in other countries</li> <li>An opportunity to leverage bleeding edge technology and industry-leading development practices</li> <li>Close collaboration with leading projects in the space</li> <li>Be part of a growing Web3 community and movement where you get to meet like minded people</li> <li>Be part of a startup that’s growing fast, packed with career opportunities in a new Web3 world and be surrounded by exceptionally talented colleagues from over all over the world</li> </ul> <p><strong>Some of our guiding principles</strong></p> <ul> <li> <strong>Dream Big: </strong>We have the ambition to become one of the core building blocks upon which the decentralized web will be built.</li> <li> <strong>Self-Mastery: </strong>Mindful conduct and always on learning are critical components of personal and collective growth.</li> <li> <strong>Collaboration:</strong> Expertise is key, but sharing knowledge and building together with joy is the foundation for truly remarkable work.</li> <li> <strong>Stay lean:</strong> Our ethos is to create and share value equitably, with minimal value extraction and that is reflected in everything we do.</li> </ul> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Boson Protocol</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>marketing-manager, growth, growth-marketing, marketing, non-tech, remote, nft, react</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49503</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2023 10:10:34 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Growth Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MDM1kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Staking Rewards</strong></p> <p>Staking Rewards is on a mission to make Staking safe and easy. We are 20 people who operate a website that is used by 250,000 people every month and an API that is used by Bloomberg, Binance, Coinbase, etc.</p> <p>We are backed by some of the world's best investors ( i.e. Galaxy Digital, Coinshares, Digital Currency Group).</p> <p>We are now at a crucial stage in our journey as the activity in staking is exploding. There are a ton of challenges facing us to unlock massive growth for Staking Rewards. However, with the right mindset, strategy, and the world-class team that we’re building, we know we can push forward.</p> <p>This Role is fully remote but limited to GMT +/- 3.</p> <p></p> <p></p> <p><strong>Our Expectations for the Role</strong></p> <ul> <li>Lead user growth efforts/campaigns for stakingrewards.com (I.e. SEO, Co-Marketing, Content etc)</li> <li>Lead the creation of compelling and authentic stories around our products</li> <li>Lead the written and visual content output on all media (newsletter, youtube, twitter, reddit)</li> <li>Grow the brand perception of Staking Rewards from a well-established niche project to a global fintech giant</li> </ul> <p></p> <p><strong>What we offer</strong></p> <ul> <li>You will be responsible for driving 100,000s of new users to a growing player in the crypto/fintech space </li> <li>You will be responsible for 100,000s of new users to discover the simplicity to gain agency over their investments and earn passive income with crypto</li> <li>You get a unique opportunity to drive bold growth efforts and experiment fast with a well established, and differentiated brand in the crypto space</li> <li>We are young, flexible, and agile. If you are dedicated and eager to learn - you will make a real difference at Staking Rewards over the years to come.</li> <li>We pay top-of-the-market salaries for high-achievers.</li> </ul> <p></p> <p></p> <p><strong>What your Profile could look like</strong></p> <ul> <li>Track-Record in driving at least 1000 Subscribers/Follower/Sign-Ups for any project (e.g. SM account or website)</li> <li>In-Depth Understanding of DeFi/Staking</li> <li>Journalistic Experience</li> <li>Strong SEO Experience</li> </ul> <p></p> <p><strong>How to apply</strong></p> <p>No lengthy process, just submit your social accounts (Twitter, LinkedIn, personal website) here. We're looking forward to hearing from you.</p> <p></p> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Staking Rewards</company>
<location> Europe worldwide</location>
<tags>growth, remote, crypto, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49483</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2023 23:04:35 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Partnerships Lead</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MDO0kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Soho</strong></p><br><p>Soho is a web3 company based in New York. We’re building a new platform to help creators and collectors discover, track, and invest in digital collectibles. Our mobile app, currently in private beta, is showing strong traction and has amassed over 45K people on the waitlist.</p><br><p>We founded Soho in 2022 with a team from Instagram, where we worked together on creator and commerce products. We’re backed by notable VCs, including Khosla Ventures and Collab+Currency, and angels from Meta, Patreon, and OpenSea.</p><br><p><strong>About the Role</strong></p><br><p>We’re hiring a Partnerships Lead with a passion for growing consumer products. In this role, you will be responsible for driving strategic partnerships with creators, collectors, and brand organizations to grow our platform's customers and ecosystem. As the first partnerships hire, you will be reporting to the CEO, cultivating the partnerships foundation and process, and working closely with a team of product designers and engineers.</p><br><p><strong>What You'll Do</strong></p><br><ul> <li>Develop and execute a comprehensive partnerships strategy that aligns with our company's goals and targets high-value partnerships.</li> <li>Identify and engage with potential partners, including creators, collectors, and brand organizations, to establish and grow mutually beneficial relationships.</li> <li>Negotiate and close partnership deals, including co-marketing initiatives, product integrations, and revenue-sharing agreements.</li> <li>Collaborate with our product, design, and engineering teams to identify opportunities for platform enhancements, new features, and marketing campaigns that can drive customer acquisition and engagement through partnerships.</li> <li>Monitor and report on partnership performance metrics, analyzing data and providing insights to guide decision-making.</li> </ul><br><p><strong>What We're Looking For</strong></p><br><ul> <li>4+ years of partnerships or business development experience, including a track record of successfully closing strategic deals.</li> <li>Proven experience of driving partnerships process, including understanding business and customer needs, identifying valuable partners, negotiating and closing deals, and executing marketing campaigns and product integrations.</li> <li>Excellent negotiator and communicator –you can build and maintain relationships with partners and drive financial/growth outcomes.</li> <li>Independent – you can work independently in a fast-paced, dynamic environment, with a strong sense of ownership and proactiveness.</li> <li>Entrepreneurial mindset – you arecustomer-focused, goal-driven, resourceful, and a quick learner eager to roll up your sleeves and tackle any tasks.</li> <li>Analytical –you can conduct market research, data analysis and user sentiment to identify partnership opportunities and make informed decisions.</li> <li>Open to travel–you can attend industry events and meetings with our our partners.</li> </ul><br><p><strong>Nice to Have</strong></p><br><ul> <li>Passionate about web3 and the creator economy</li> <li>Experience with consumer social, e-commerce, and/or blockchain technology</li> <li>Willingness to adjust to new priorities in a fast-paced environment</li> <li>Dog friendly :)</li> </ul><br><p><strong>Our Benefits</strong></p><br><ul> <li>Competitive salary and equity in the company</li> <li>Premium medical, dental, and vision plans</li> <li>Private office space in downtown Manhattan</li> <li>Work equipment (laptop, accessories, etc)</li> <li>Generous PTO and sick leave policy</li> <li>Flexible work hours</li> </ul><br> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Soho</company>
<location> NY New York US</location>
<tags>partnership, sales, non-tech, lead, blockchain</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49482</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2023 22:42:50 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Licensing Compliance Manager</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=IDO0kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="single-job-content body3 block" id="tabpanel-0" aria-labelledby="tab-0" role="tabpanel"> <div class="content-intro"> <p><span>At Ripple, we’re building a world where value moves like information does today. It’s big, it’s bold, and we’re already doing it. Through our crypto solutions for financial institutions, businesses, governments and developers, we are improving the global financial system and creating greater economic fairness and opportunity for more people, in more places around the world. And we get to do the best work of our career and grow our skills surrounded by colleagues who have our backs. </span></p> <p><span>If you’re ready to see your impact and unlock incredible career growth opportunities, join us, and build real world value.</span></p> </div> <div> <p><strong>THE WORK:</strong></p> <p><span>Ripple is expanding its team and seeks to hire an experienced Licensing Compliance Manager. This role will be focused on assisting the Licensing Compliance Project Director with multiple global licensing work streams as Ripple continues to launch various regulated products and services throughout the world.</span></p> <p><strong>WHAT YOU’LL DO:</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>Prepare license application forms, apply for licenses, and communicate progress with various internal stakeholders</span></li> <li><span>Engage with cross-functional stakeholders (e.g., Product, Legal, Compliance, Policy, and Engineering) to establish a thoughtful strategic and tactical approach to licensing applications and related processes</span></li> <li><span>Assist with the development of internal policies, procedures, and frameworks to ensure compliance with requirements under new and existing licenses</span></li> <li><span>Manage regulatory reporting requirements by gathering data from multiple sources, harmonizing collected data, and submitting the compiled report in a timely manner</span></li> <li><span>Oversee the day-to-day maintenance of licenses, including license renewals as well as preparation of responses to requests for information</span></li> <li><span>Frequently engage with the supervisory teams of the various regulatory bodies that oversee Ripple’s activity. Participate in regulatory examinations and thematic inspections</span></li> <li><span>Carry out ad hoc projects necessary to advance Ripple’s global licensing efforts</span></li> </ul> </div> <div> <p><strong>WHAT YOU'LL BRING: </strong></p> </div> <div> <ul> <li><span>5+ years of experience in regulatory compliance within the FinTech or virtual asset industries</span></li> <li><span>Proven track record of successfully collaborating with representatives from cross-functional teams (e.g., Product, Legal, Compliance, Policy, and Engineering) in order to ensure compliance with regulatory requirements and industry best practices</span></li> <li><span>Experience with interacting with financial regulators, managing regulatory examinations, and maintaining licenses (e.g. regulatory reporting); NMLS, FCA Connect, and CBI Online Reporting System experience a plus</span></li> <li><span>Strong organizational skills with proven ability to work within and meet deadlines in a fast-paced environment</span></li> <li><span>Understanding of the requirements and expectations of global regulatory bodies in the virtual asset and payments space; preferably in the United States, Ireland, United Kingdom, and Singapore</span></li> <li><span>High attention to detail working in a strict deadline-driven environment</span></li> <li><span>Advanced analytical and research skills, and desire to create documentation and internal reporting </span></li> <li><span>Strong process and project management skills with attention to detail, proactive and able to quickly adapt to changes</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Other common names for this role: </span></p> </div> <div class="content-conclusion"> <hr> <p><strong>WHO WE ARE:</strong></p> <p><span>Do Your Best Work</span></p> <ul> <li><span>The opportunity to build in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders</span></li> <li><span>A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact.  A professional development budget to support other modes of learning.</span></li> <li><span>Thrive in an environment where no matter what race, ethnicity, gender, origin, or culture they identify with, every employee is a respected, valued, and empowered part of the team.</span></li> <li><span>Ripple is Flexible First: you have the option to work from home, from our offices, or a combination of the two around our centers of gravity (15 global offices).</span></li> <li><span>Weekly all-company meeting - business updates and ask me anything &gt;</span></li> <li><span>We come together for moments that matter which include team offsites, team bonding activities, happy hours and more!</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Control of Your Finances</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Competitive salary, bonuses, and equity</span></li> <li><span>Competitive benefits that cover physical and mental healthcare, retirement, family forming, and family support</span></li> <li><span>Employee giving match</span></li> <li><span>Mobile phone stipend</span></li> </ul> <p><span>Take Care of Yourself</span></p> <ul> <li><span>Twice a quarter R&amp;R days so you can rest and recharge</span></li> <li><span>Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite &amp; virtual programming</span></li> <li><span>Generous vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it</span></li> <li><span>Industry-leading parental leave policies. Family planning benefits.</span></li> <li><span>Catered lunches, fully-stocked kitchens with premium snacks/beverages, and plenty of fun events</span></li> </ul> <p><span><em data-stringify-type="italic">Benefits listed above are for full-time employees.</em></span></p> <hr> <div><em>Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.</em></div> <div> </div> <div><em>Please find our UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice and our California Applicant Privacy Notice for reference.</em></div> </div> <p></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Ripple</company>
<location>Dublin, Ireland</location>
<tags>compliance, non-tech, crypto</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49479</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2023 17:42:53 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Lead Software Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=kzN0kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p><strong><em>Do you self-identify as a great problem solver (not just a coder)?</em></strong></p> <p><strong><em>Have you been honing your innovation craft for years yet yearning for more complex challenges?</em></strong></p> <p><strong><em>Does the opportunity to play a key role in the launch of a software platform with massive impact (for millions or even billions of people) excite you?</em></strong></p> <p><strong><em>If you’ve answered with 3 resounding yeses, then we want to meet you! </em></strong></p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>What We Expect</strong></p> <p>We are a cutting-edge web3 infrastructure scale-up project seeking a few very talented developers who are not just looking for a job but want to be challenged to accomplish great things in an exciting venture. </p> <p>We are the veterans of many successful startups and will put you on the accelerated learning curve toward your future success.</p> <p>This position requires a great understanding of large-scale distributed computing and web3 technologies. Yet, we are open to talented people with less experience in web3 but have experience building large, robust data solutions and are eager to grow into web3.  </p> <p>You'll be immediately challenged to take ownership of key development track(s) within one of our innovation squads: 1. Decentralized Data Cloud Squad, 2. Blockchain Squad, 3. Tools, Services &amp; Integrations Squad.</p> <p>Once placed in a squad, you will own and drive the design, prototyping, testing/implementation (yes, tests are an integral part of implementation), simulating, and CI/CD of key components of our platform in a highly collaborative and iterative manner across squads.</p> <p><br><strong>About Cere Network</strong></p> <p>Cere Network is the decentralized data protocol powering the future of web3 with trustless content sharing and cloud data interactions between apps, users, AI/ML, and (NFT) assets. Cere is backed by the world’s largest institutions and projects, including Binance Labs, Republic Labs, and Polygon.</p> <p><br><strong>Our Ethos</strong></p> <p>We look for a few things across all hires we make at Cere, regardless of role or team: </p> <p>- We seek teammates who will thrive in our fast-paced work environment, where we default to methodical, simulation-driven, fast development iterations and a first-principle thinking mindset. </p> <p>- We crave teammates with high standards and strong discipline, embracing a growth mindset to continuously learn and incrementally improve habits and processes. </p> <p>- We require contributors to have excellent communication skills (esp. written), for everything must be well organized and tracked in Notion, Slack, Wiki’s, etc. We want autonomous, goal-oriented individuals who embrace transparency and accountability. No one wants to micro-manage others.</p> <p>- We need good teammates who are generally cool people who want to be part of a great team &amp; decentralized community where everyone truly helps and challenges each other to learn/grow by innovating together towards greater shared goals. Embracing the building of such a collaborative community is the only way we can sustain rapid innovation (and the only way to live/work, really).</p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>Requirements:</strong></p> <p>- 5+ years of experience (preferred 10+) working as a software engineer on storage and distributed systems.</p> <p>- Extensive programming experience with at least one modern language such as Go, Rust, Typescript, Java or Kotlin.</p> <p>- In-depth understanding of decentralized systems, blockchain, and web3, as well as system design, data structures, and algorithms.</p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>Nice to have:</strong></p> <p>- Expertise in database engine internals (storage), including indexing, access methods, concurrency control, logging, caching, transaction processing, replication, backup restore, and buffer management.</p> <p>- Proficiency in database engine internals (query processing), such as query compilation, optimization, execution, and parallel execution.</p> <p>- Experience with decentralized storage systems like IPFS.</p> <p>- Experience developing SDKs and contributing to open-source projects.</p> <p>- Knowledge of distributed systems, including consensus-based quorum replication and NoSQL system implementation.</p> <p><br></p> <p><strong>A bit more about our Multinational, High-Performance (and primarily remote) Team</strong></p> <p>Join a highly talented multicultural team that is based all over the world. We have offices in San Francisco, New York, Warsaw, Amsterdam, Berlin, and several locations in Asia. As stated above, we make remote working possible by embracing our ethos, yet many teams also travel to meet in person every 1-2 months. We all want high degrees of autonomy and flexibility to make life and work fun, but transparency, accountability/ownership are the requisites.</p> <p><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>CERE NETWORK</company>
<location>Remote or/and Europe</location>
<tags>dev, lead, blockchain, decentralize, golang, java, kotlin, nft, rust, typescript, web3, remote</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49473</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2023 10:33:33 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Senior Product Manager, Financial Hub</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=MzN0kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="content-intro"> <p><span>At Coinbase, our mission is to</span><span> </span><span>increase economic freedom around the world</span><span>, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web3 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.</span></p> <p><span>There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a</span><span> </span><span>culture</span><span> like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our</span><span> </span><span>mission-focused approach</span><span> to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.</span></p> <p><strong>Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.</span></li> <li><span>You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.</span></li> <li><span>You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.</span></li> <li><span>You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.</span></li> <li><span>You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.</span></li> <li><span>You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. </span></li> </ul> </div><p><span>The Financial Hub team at Coinbase is key to Coinbase’s mission to create an open financial system for the world. The Financial Hub team powers all crypto &amp; fiat money movements on Coinbase, and powers both our core trading business and our ambitious venture bets in crypto. In this role you will lead a financial platform that handles hundreds of billions of dollars in transaction volume each year.</span></p> <p><span><br></span><span>We are looking for an entrepreneurial, self-motivated Product Manager who thrives in a fast-paced startup environment. You will be comfortable dealing with ambiguity, able to think through complex challenges, and able to align cross-functional teams effectively to launch products. Knowledge and experience in financial products, data platform technologies, and/or crypto products are value-adds for this role.</span></p> <p></p> <p><strong>What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>Define and build out Coinbase’s Financial Hub roadmap, including building new financial vehicles, new crypto experiences, and the platforms that serve all our users globally</span></li> <li><span>Own product development from conception to launch</span></li> <li><span>Collaborate cross-functionally with engineering, data, and cross-functional teams to develop and steer product roadmap</span></li> <li><span>Define and analyze metrics to guide product development</span></li> <li><span>Align teams on a shared vision and steer execution on that vision.</span></li> </ul> <p><strong>What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):</strong></p> <ul> <li><span>5+ years of product management experience, knowledge of financial products is preferred</span></li> <li><span>Demonstrated ability to motivate and align large cross-functional teams towards a common vision</span></li> <li><span>Deep analytical, prioritization and problem solving skills</span></li> <li><span>Computer Science or Software Engineering background preferred</span></li> <li><span>An entrepreneurial mindset with the ability to succeed in a fast-paced environment</span></li> </ul> <p><br><br></p> <p></p> <p></p> <p></p> <p><span>Pay Transparency Notice: Depending on your work location, the target annual salary for this position can range from $201,450 to $237,000 + target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).</span></p> <p><em><span>Position ID: G2024</span></em></p><div class="content-conclusion"> <h4><span>Commitment to Equal Opportunity</span></h4> <p><span>Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law. For US applicants, you may viewPay Transparency,Employee RightsandKnow Your Rightsnotices by clicking on their corresponding links. Additionally, Coinbase participates in theE-Verify programin certain locations, as required by law.</span><span></span></p> <p><span>Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to </span><span>accommodations[at]coinbase.com</span><span> and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information. For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site </span><span>click here to download</span><span> a free compatible screen reader </span><span>(free step by step tutorial can be found here)</span><span>.</span></p> <h4><span>Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants</span></h4> <p><span>Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available here. </span><span>By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required. For US applicants only, by submitting your application you are agreeing to arbitration of disputes as outlined here. </span></p> <p></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>Coinbase</company>
<location> Remote - USA</location>
<tags>finance, non-tech, product-manager, senior, remote, crypto, defi</tags>
</item>
<item>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49468</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 1 May 2023 00:11:22 +0700</pubDate>
<title>Senior Solidity Engineer</title>
<link>https://web3.career/r/=gjN0kDN__wk1uGt</link>
<description><![CDATA[<div class="trix-content"> <p><strong>Who We Are</strong></p> <p>GammaSwap is building a novel oracle free volatility DEX where users can short the liquidity inside any AMM and any liquidity pool. This could be used to hedge Impermanent Loss or to long volatility on a token pair.<br><br></p> <p>We also have ideas for novel products that will change DeFi as we know it touching every major category. We will need your help building those.<br><br></p> <p>As a team, we value the freedom to work anywhere in the world, constructive and open dialogues, and credibly neutral protocols.<br><br></p> <p><strong>Who You Are</strong><br><br>A senior level engineer with a background in developing Solidity based smart contracts. You have at least two years of experience (or equivalent knowledge) in developing high-performing blockchain apps or smart contracts and can provide code samples that demonstrate this.<br><br></p> <p>A passion for building bleeding-edge technology on the blockchain and pushing forward innovation in DeFi. You’re a creative thinker and analytical problem solver who is inspired by the opportunity to build new startups and products and is unafraid to push the boundaries of what’s possible with technology. You possess a deep mastery of other open-source technologies that power the web. You can write and speak fluent English.<br><br></p> <p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p> <ul> <li>Design and build complex automated strategies using vaults</li> <li>Envision and develop features to help build new applications</li> <li>Implement algorithms developed for our novel AMM</li> <li>Collaborate with the team and cross-functional partners on all aspects of product development.</li> <li>Identify and advocate for team-wide areas of improvement and best practices.</li> <li>Mentor team members to refine their technical and architectural skills.</li> <li>Take a security first approach to smart contract development</li> </ul> <p><strong>Requirements</strong><br><br></p> <ul> <li>Experience owning and shipping multiple products</li> <li>3+ years of industry experience in software engineering preferably in a low level language like C++</li> <li>Strong Solidity understanding, preferably with at least one project shipped to mainnet</li> <li>3+ years of Solidity experience</li> <li>Ability to quickly iterate and ship code using test-driven development patterns</li> <li>Experience with version control, such as Git</li> <li>Knowledge of engineering best practices such as continuous integration</li> <li>Exceptional judgment, problem-solving skills, and an analytical mindset</li> <li>Ability to work in areas beyond your comfort zone and motivated by personal growth</li> <li>A passion for learning and a self-awareness of your learning style</li> </ul> <p><br></p> </div> When applying, mention the word CANDYSHOP to show you read the job post completely.]]></description>
<company>GammaSwap Labs</company>
<location>Remote</location>
<tags>dev, senior, ethereum, blockchain, c-plus-plus, defi, solidity, remote</tags>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>